- 路易斯在哪? - 嘿 大家好
- Where's Louis? - Hey, guys.
快来 快来
Come on, come on.
大家都有很多很复杂的情绪
There's a lot of mixed emotions in general.
就像 怎么去解释14年?
It's like, how do you explain 14 years?
没法解释
It's like, it's impossible to do,
但是 它彻底地改变了我们的生活 让我们的生活很精彩
but it's completely changed our lives for the good.
- 最后一次这么走了 路易斯 对不? - 这不会是最后一次
- Final walk, Louis, eh? - It's not the final walk.
哦 他动情咯
Oh, he's getting emotional already.
- 是哦 我们得让他走着 - 他已经进入状态了
- It is. We got to get him going there. - He's getting emotional already.
谁带着棺材?
Who's carrying the coffin?
每个人的梦想都不同
Everybody's dream is different.
但是 我们四个在一起 这正是我们想要的
But the four of us, that's what we wanted.
你知道 我们一直都想成为著名的流行歌手
You know, we always wanted to be famous pop stars.
你得明白它是什么...
You have to be able to, you know, grab it for what it is
能说出:"这真不可思议"
"and say,"That was amazing."
14年 14年 我们将要在这里结束
Fourteen years. Fourteen years, we're ending it here, huh.
谢谢各位 谢谢
Thanks, guys. Thanks.
尽情享受 尽情享受
- Enjoy. - Enjoy.
就像有人在我17岁的时候给我写了一封信
It's like somebody wrote me a letter when I was 17
说:"你会去环游世界十次"
and going,"You're gonna travel the world 10 times over,
"你会卖出四千五百万张唱片 你会遇到今生的最爱"
"you're gonna sell 45 million records, you're gonna meet the love of your life.
"你会赚很多钱"
"You're gonna have lots of money
"从此过着幸福的生活"
"and live the rest of your life as happy as possible."
就是这样 这就是过去发生的一切
That's... That's it. That's what happened.
我们做得不赖哈 是不是 路易斯?
Well, we didn't do bad, did we, Louis?
就是这样的事情
You know it's kind of one of those things.
有点难以想象哈
It's hard to, kind of, figure out in your head even.
一种快乐与悲伤混杂在一起的感觉
You know, it is a happy and sad moment, all in one feeling.
在内心深处 我们不希望结束 就像 我们说的那样
Deep down we don't want it to end, like, all of us will tell you that.
但是 我们知道一切不得不结束
But we know it has to
未来是未可知的 和现在完全不同的境地
It's the unknown, it's a different place.
你们将从曾经的西域男孩的生活中走出来
You're out of that Westlife bubble that you've been in,
那种"西域男孩时代"所拥有的保护和安全感
that protection, that security of, you know, being in Westlife.
就像 我们一直都是西域男孩的一员 我们所有人都是
Like, we'll always be a member of Westlife, you know, all of us.
我可以说我是西域男孩
I can always say I'm a member of Westlife.
但是 我们将不再是一个乐队
But, you know, we won't be a band any more.
所以 将会……难以面对的
So it will be... it will be kind of scary.
这些所有的经历
The whole experience,
没有人能明白 我是说 我们四个人...
nobody will ever, ever understand it, I mean, the four of us,
因为 你知道 我们之间的关系非常非常非常紧密
because, you know, we've become a very, very, very tight bunch of lads.
我不知道
I don't know.
我们即将要踏上的……
We're about to embark on, you know
是目前为止我们事业中最苦涩最甜蜜的旅程
the most kind of bitter sweet journey of our career so far.
长远看来
The bigger picture, in the long term.
这是我们告别之旅
And it's our last ever tour,
显然 这是很痛苦一个方面
so obviously that's the kind of bitter side of it.
是我们非常不愿意看到的一面
the side that we're obviously not looking forward to.
就好像是最后一章
It's kind of the final chapter, I suppose,
在《西域男孩》这本书里 是不?
in the book of Westlife nom isn't it?
我们将在巅峰退去 在某个时刻退去
We're going out on top. We're going out at a time
或许人们会说 这个时候太早或者太晚
where people might say it might be too soon or might be too late.
但是 我们觉得现在是最佳时机
But we feel it's the right time
我希望这个乐队会永远存在
You know I think we kept it going.
而这对我们或者西域男孩是不公平的
We felt it wouldn't have been fair to us or to Westlife, you know
我们想要用一种很愉快的方式来结束这一切
because we want to end this on a very happy note.
而且 最重要的是 我们四个人是非常好的朋友
And the four of us are very good friends, which is most important.
这是我们14年全部生活的结束
It's the end of you know, what has been the last 14 years of all of our lives.
从我们少年开始 我们都知道的
You know since we were teenagers, this is now all we know.
但 在14年中我第一次非常相信
But I do believe that for the first time in 14 years
我们四个真的要分道扬镳了
that the four of us are now really entering the abyss.
这是个很可怕的想法 毫无疑问
It's a scary, scary thought there's no doubt about it.
它的确非常非常让人难过
It's very, very scary.
从成为西域男孩开始 它就成为我的全部
Being a member of Westlife from the start has been my whole world.
一直是
It's been, you know
从我的儿童时代 这一直是我的梦想
from my childhood, it's been everything I've dreamed of.
在舞台上成为一名表演者
You know to be a performer on the stage
并且成为我的职业 这个梦想实现了
and for that to be my"job", you know has been a dream come true.
所以 14年以后 我们决定某天解散
So, you know after 14 years we've kinda made the decision to call it a day
这个巡演 我们将称作是告别之旅
and this tour that we're about to do is The Farewell Tour
所以 将会是一个十分动人之旅
so it's gonna be a very big emotional ride
现在 点燃激情吧！来吧 各位！
Now, light this up! Come on, buddy!
最后一次
One last time.
# 空虚的心被阴影填满 #
# Shadows fill an empty heart #
# 因为爱已经褪色 #
# As love is fading #
# 我们经历的所有 #
# From all the things that we are #
# 都已经沉默不语 #
# But are not saying #
# 我们能穿越那些伤疤 #
# Can we see beyond the scars #
# 而让曙光降临么? #
# And make it to the dawn? #
# 改变天空的颜色 #
# Change the colours of the sky #
# 敞开胸怀 #
# And open up to #
# 那些你让我觉得我还活着的方式 #
# The ways you made me feel alive #
# 我爱你的方式 #
# The ways I loved you #
# 爱是永远不会磨灭的 #
# For all the things that never died #
# 让它们穿越无尽的黑暗 #
# To make it through the night #
# 爱最终会找到你 #
# Love will find you #
# 那么现在呢? 今天该怎么办呢? #
# What about now? What about today? #
# 如果你让我成为我曾经想成为的那个人会怎么样呢? #
# What if you're making me all that I was meant to be? #
# 如果我们的爱永远不会离去呢 #?
# What if our love never went away? #
# 如果我们再也找不到那些 未曾说出口的话语呢? #
# What if it's lost behind words we could never find? #
# 宝贝 在一切都太迟之前 #
# Baby, before it's too late #
Croke Park 跟我一起唱！
Sing it, Croke Park!
# 那道从你眼中闪耀出的光芒 #
# The sun is breaking in your eyes #
# 开启了新的一天 #
# To start a new day #
# 这颗破碎了的心依然可以存活 #
# This broken heart can still survive #
# 只需你赐给我慈悲 #
# With a touch of your grace #
# 阴影隐进光芒里 #
# Shadows fade into the light #
# 而我在你身边 #
# I am by your side #
# 在爱可以找到你的地方 #
# Where love will find you #
# 那么现在呢?那么今天呢? #
# What about now? What about today? #
# 如果你让我成为 我曾经想成为的那个人会怎么样呢? #
# What if you're making me all that I was meant to be? #
# 如果我们的爱永远不会离去呢? #
# What if our love never went away? #
# 如果我们再也找不到 那些未曾说出口的话语呢? #
# What if it's lost behind words we could never find #
# 宝贝 在一切都太迟之前 #
# Baby, before it's too late #
# 那么现在呢? #
# What about now? #
# 现在我们都在这里 #
# Now that we're here #
# 现在我们都已经跋涉了这么远 #
# Now that we've come this far #
# 只是再坚持一下 #
# just hold on #
# 没什么值得畏惧的 #
# There is nothing to fear #
# 因为我一直在你左右 #
# For I am right beside you #
# 一辈子 #
# For all my life #
# 我是属于你的 #
# I am yours #
# 那么现在呢?那么今天呢? #
# What about now? What about today? #
# 如果你让我成为我 曾经想成为的那个人会怎么样呢? #
# What if you're making me all that I was meant to be? #
# 如果我们的爱永远不会离去呢? #
# What if our love never went away? #
# 如果我们再也找不到那些未曾说出口的话语呢? #
# What if it's lost behind words we could never find #
# 那么现在呢? 那么今天呢? #
# What about now? What about today? #
# 如果你让我成为我曾经想成为的那个人会怎么样呢? #
# What if you're making me all that I was meant to be? #
# 如果我们的爱永远不会离去呢? #
# What if our love never went away? #
# 如果我们再也找不到那些未曾说出口的话语呢? #
# What if it's lost behind words we could never find #
# 宝贝 在一切都太晚之前 #
# Baby, before it's too late #
# 那么现在呢? #
# What about now? #
# 哦 耶 #
# Oh, yeah #
# 这是该再见 #
# This is goodbye #
# 空虚的心被阴影填满 #
#  Shadows fill an empty heart  #
# 这不是再见 #
# This isn't goodbye #
# 我发誓我们会哭泣 #
# And I swear we will cry #
# 就算我看着你离去 #
# Even as I watch you leave #
# 这不是再见 #
# This is isn't goodbye #
# 如果是其他的女孩,我想我舍得她离开 #
# Cause any other girl, I'd let you walk away #
# 如果是其他的女孩,我相信我肯定不会那么伤心 #
# Any other girl, I'm sure I'd be 0k #
# 告诉我怎么做一个好男人 #
# Tell me what makes a man #
# 他想要全心全意的对你好 #
# Wanna give you all his heart #
# 当你在他身边的时候他微笑 #
# Smile when you're around #
# 当你离开的时候他却在哭泣 #
# And cry when you're apart #
# 如果你知道怎样做一个好男人 #
# If you know what makes a man #
# 想要你爱的人像我这样爱你 #
# Wanna love you the way I do #
# 女孩,你一定要让我知道 #
# Girl, you gotta let me know #
# 你们唱 #
You sing. #
# 这样我才能忘记你 #
# So I can get over you #
# 是什么让你对她一见钟情? #
# What makes her so right? #
# 是她的笑声吗? #
# is it the sound of her laugh? #
# 还是她的眼睛? #
# That look in her eyes #
# 什么时候你能决定? #
# When do you decide? #
# 她就是你追寻的梦 #
# She is the dream that you seek #
# 她是你生命中动力的源泉 #
# That force in your life #
# 你会向她道歉,不论谁对谁错 #
# When you apologise, no matter who was wrong #
# 你愿意为了她放弃自己的一切 #
# When you get on your knees if that would bring her home #
# 告诉我怎样做一个好男人 #
# Tell me what makes a man #
# 他想要全心全意的对你好 #
# Wanna give you all his heart #
# 当你在他身边的时候他微笑 #
# Smile when you're around #
# 当你离开的时候他会哭泣 #
# And cry when you're apart #
# 如果你知道怎样做一个好男人 #
# If you know what makes a man #
# 想要你爱的人像我这样爱你 #
# Wanna love you the way I do #
# 女孩 你一定要让我知道 #
# Girl, you gotta let me know #
# 这样我才能忘记你 #
# So I can get over you #
# 我的生命中其他的女孩会一如既往的出现 #
# Other girls will come along, they always do #
# 但是为什么我还是此强烈的需要你 #
# What's the point when all I ever want is you #
# 请告诉我 #
# Tell me #
# 告诉我怎样做一个好男人 #
# Tell me what makes a man #
# 他想要全心全意的对你好 #
# Wanna give you all his heart #
# 当你在他身边的时候他微笑 #
# Smile when you're around #
# 当你离开的时候他会哭泣 #
# And cry when you're apart #
# 如果你知道怎样做一个好男人 #
# If you know what makes a man #
# 想要你爱的人像我这样爱你 #
# Wanna love you the way I do #
# 女孩 你一定要让我知道 #
# Girl, you gotta let me know #
# 你一定要让我知道 #
# You gotta let me know #
# 女孩 你一定要让我知道 #
# Girl, you gotta let me know #
# 这样我才能忘记你 #
# So I can get over you #
# 空寂的街道,空寂的房间 #
# An empty street An empty house #
# 空寂的思念深藏在我的心中 #
# A hole inside my heart #
# 孤孤单单,无尽的孤寂压迫着我 #
# I'm all alone, the rooms are getting smaller #
# 我想知道怎样,我想知道是何原因 #
# I wonder how I wonder why #
# 我想知道他们的归属 #
# I wonder where they are #
# 我们在一起的时光 我们共同吟唱的歌曲 #
# The days we had, the songs we sang together #
# 哦 耶 #
# Oh, yeah #
# 还有你 我的爱人 #
# And oh, my love #
# 我始终坚持着 #
# I'm holding on forever #
# 但得到一份爱却是那样遥不可及 #
# Reaching for a love that seems so far #
唱吧！
Sing!
# 我稍稍向上帝祈求 #
# So I say a little prayer #
# 并希望我的梦想能带我到那儿 #
# And hope my dreams will take me there #
# 那儿有湛蓝的天空还有你美丽的笑容 #
# Where the skies are blue to see you once again #
# 我的爱人 #
# My love #
# 漂过大海 翻山越岭 #
# Overseas from coast to coast #
# 去找寻一个我最喜爱的地方 #
# To find the place I love the most #
# 那儿有翠绿的草原还有你醉人的眼神 #
# Where the fields are green to see you once again #
# 我的爱人 #
# My love #
# 我甜蜜的爱人 #
# My sweet love #
# 我尝试阅读 我尽力工作 #
# I try to read I go to work #
# 我和我的朋友逍遥狂欢 #
# I'm laughing with my friends #
# 但这一切都不能阻止我的幻想 #
# But I can't stop to keep myself from thinking #
# 我想知道怎样 我想知道是何原因 #
# I wonder how I wonder why #
# 我想知道他们的归属 #
# I wonder where they are #
# 我们在一起的时光 我们共同吟唱的歌曲 #
# The days we had, the songs we sang together #
# 哦 耶 #
# Oh, yeah #
# 还有你 我的爱人 #
# And oh, my love #
# 我始终坚持着 #
# I'm holding on forever #
# 但得到一份爱却是那样遥不可及v
# Reaching for the love that seems so far #
# 我稍稍向上帝请求 #
# So I say a little prayer #
# 并希望我的梦想能带我到那儿 #
# And hope my dreams will take me there #
# 那儿有湛蓝的天空还有你美丽的笑容 #
# Where the skies are blue to see you once again #
# 我的爱人 #
# My love #
# 漂过大海 翻山越岭 #
# Overseas from coast to coast #
# 去找寻一个我最喜爱的地方 #
# To find the place I love the most #
# 还有翠绿的草原上飘扬的你 #
# Where the fields are green to see you once again #
# 我想抱紧你 #
# To hold you in my arms #
# 我向你保证 我的爱人 #
# To promise you my love #
# 我绝不是在撒谎 #
# To tell you from my heart #
# 你是我所想的一切 #
# You're all I'm thinking of #
尖叫吧 爱尔兰
Ireland, scream if you feel good.
好的 大家一起来
All right! Come on, everybody,
让我看到你们挥舞的双手
let me see your hands go up and side to side.
所有在场的人 大家一起来！
Everybody in the stadium, do it!
# 但得到一份爱却是那样遥不可及 #
# Reaching for the love that seems so far #
# 我稍稍向上帝祈求 稍稍向上帝祈求 #
# So I say a little prayer # say a prayer #
# 并希望我的梦想能带我到那儿 带我到那儿 #
# Hope my dreams will take me there # Take me there #
# 那儿有湛蓝的天空还有你美丽的笑容 #
# Where the skies are blue to see you once again #
# 我的爱人 #
# My love #
# 漂过大海 翻山越岭 漂过大海 #
# Overseas from coast to coast # Overseas #
# 去找寻一个我最喜爱的地方 我最喜爱的地方 #
# To find the place I love the most # I love the most #
# 那儿有翠绿的草原还有你醉人的眼神 #
# Where the fields are green to see you once again #
唱起来 都柏林
Sing, Dublin!
# 我稍稍向上帝祈求 #
# Say a little prayer #
# 并希望我的梦想能带我到那儿 #
# Dreams will take me there # Take me there #
# 那儿有湛蓝的天空还有你美丽的笑容 #
# Where the skies are blue to see you once again #
# 我的爱人 #
# My love #
# 漂过大海 翻山越岭 翻山越岭 #
# Overseas from coast to coast # Coast to coast #
# 去找寻一个我最喜爱的地方 最喜爱的地方 #
# To find the place I love the most # Love the most #
# 那儿有翠绿的草原还有你醉人的眼神 #
# Where the fields are green to see you once again #
# 我稍稍向上帝祈求 稍稍的祈求 #
# Say a little prayer # Say a prayer #
# 并希望我的梦想能带我到那儿 带我到那儿 #
# Dreams will take me there # Take me there #
# 那儿有湛蓝的天空还有你美丽的笑容 #
# Where the skies are blue to see you once again #
# 我的爱人 我的爱人 我的爱人 #
# My love, my love, my love #
# 漂过大海 翻山越岭 翻山越岭 #
# Overseas from coast to coast # Coast to coast #
# 去找寻一个我最喜爱的地方 #
# To find the place I love the most # I love the most #
# 那儿有翠绿的草原还有你醉人的眼神 #
# Where the fields are green to see you once again #
# 我的爱人 #
# My love #
晚上好 Croke Park！
Good evening, Croke Park!
喔！
Whoo!
今晚大家感觉怎么样?还好吗?
How's everybody feeling tonight? All right?
让我听听Croke Park的喊声！
Let me hear Croke Park scream!
喔！
Whoo!
哇喔 怎么说呢
Wow! What can I say?
今晚站在这里 感觉真的非常棒
It really feels absolutely amazing to be up here tonight.
非常非常欢迎你们
Well, you're all very, very welcome
来到西域男孩的演唱会
to the last ever Westlife concert.
我知道
I know.
我告诉你们 85,000人哄我不好玩哦
I tell you what, it's not very pretty to have 85,000 people booing me.
兄弟们 我们一直在期待的就是这个晚上
Guys, as you all know we've all been waiting for this night
我们去年宣布这个消息后 等了很长一段时间
for a very long time when we made the announcement last year.
你知道 今天终于站在这里了 很不可思议
And you know, it's hard to believe it's here
很难以想象我们站在85,000人面前的舞台上
It's hard to believe we're up on stage in front of 85, 000 people
在我们的祖国
in our home country.
今晚 我们不仅拥有85,000的观众,
Not only do we have 85,000 people in here tonight,
在西域男孩告别演唱会之夜
on Westlife's final night
而且我们拥有成千上万来自世界各地的观众
but we have thousands of people watching all over the world
在影院观看现场直播
in the cinemas live right now.
所以 此时正在影院大屏幕观看演唱会的观众们……
So, anybody who's watching this on the big screens in the cinemas...
你们好！
Hello!
在这个西域男孩最后的演唱会
So, as this is the very last Westlife concert,
这个演唱会的主意 当我们决定要开演唱会时 所有的这些主意
the whole idea of this, the whole idea when we decided
我们找一天
that we were actually gonna call it a day,
能够来到这里再看一看我们的粉丝
was to be able to get out here and to see our fans one more time
并且庆祝我们14年来不可思议的成功
And to celebrate 14 years of amazing success.
在这里 我要说 Croke Park
I have to say, Croke Park,
再没有比这里更好的地方来开这次告别演唱会
there's no better place to be doing it than right here,
在你们所有人面前 在这个已经易主的体育馆里
in front of you guys, in this sold out stadium.
还有Dublin Nicky
In your Dublin, Nicky.
所以 朋友们 我要说...
So, guys, I have to say,
今晚是14年庆典
tonight is all about celebrating that 14 years.
你们兴奋吗?
Are you guys up for that?
我说 你们嗨吗?
I said, are you guys up for that?
我要将那些感人的东西留到后面
Good stuff I I gotta save the emotional stuff for later on.
继续表演
Let's get on with the show.
女士们 先生们 请跟着唱
Ladies and gentlemen, please sing along with this one.
歌名：这是守护
This is Safe.
# 前路崎岖坦途难觅 #
# Hard to find a way to get through #
# 满是凄凉 #
# It's a tragedy #
# 我愿像漫天繁星那样 #
# Pulling at me like the stars do #
# 围绕在你的身旁 #
# You're like gravity #
# 即使风起云涌我也不离不弃 #
# Even if the wind blows #
# 这一切看起来不可思议 #
# It makes it hard to believe #
# 你如何去爱? 爱 #
# How you gonna love # Love #
# 你如何去感觉? 感觉 #
# How you gonna feel # Feel #
# 你如何在梦境般的 #
# How you gonna live your life #
# 现实中生活? #
# like the dream you have is real #
# 如果你迷失了前路 路 #
# And if you've lost your way # Way #
# 我会一直守护着你 守护 #
# I will keep you safe # Safe #
# 敞开你的心扉吧 #
# Well, open up all the world inside #
# 期待与你共度良宵 #
# So you come alive tonight #
# 我会一直守护着你 #
# I will keep you safe #
# 不担心 #
# Does it even matter to you #
# 你看到我的种种 #
# To see what I can see #
# 我在地面上爬着抓住你 #
# I'm crawling on the floor to reach you #
# 你看到我试图挽回你 #
# I'm a wreck, you see #
# 而今当你离家远去 #
# When you're far from home now #
# 这一切看起来不可思议 #
# Makes it hard to believe #
跟我一起唱！
Sing with me!
# 你如何去爱 #
# How you gonna love #
# 你如何去感觉 #
# How you gonna feel #
# 你如何在梦境般的 #
# How you gonna live your life #
# 现实中生活 #
# like the dream you have is real #
# 如果你迷失了前路 #
# And if you've lost your way #
# 我会一直守护着你 #
# I will keep you safe #
# 敞开你的心扉吧 #
# Well, open up all the world inside #
# 今夜你将精彩绽放 #
# So you come alive tonight #
# 我会一直守护着你 #
# I will keep you safe #
# 我陪你同跌倒 #
# We all fall down #
# 我陪你共失落 #
# We all feel doubt #
# 因为在雨天和夏日里 #
# There's rainy days and summer highs #
# 我们一起祈祷 一起感受 #
# The more we break, the more we feel alive #
# 你如何去爱 #
# How you gonna love #
# 你如何去感觉 #
# How you gonna feel #
一起唱吧,Dublin,来吧
You sing it, Dublin, come on.
# 你如何在梦境般的 #
# How you gonna live your life #
# 现实中生活 #
# like the dream you have is real #
女士们 先生们 鼓掌欢迎我们的吉他手 Ben Jones先生!
Ladies and gentlemen, give it up for our guitarist, Mr. Ben Jones!
# 你如何去爱 #
# How you gonna love #
# 你如何去感觉 #
# How you gonna feel #
# 你如何在梦境般的 #
# How you gonna live your life #
# 现实中生活 #
# like the dream you have is real #
# 如果你迷失了前路 #
# And if you've lost your way #
# 我会一直守护着你 #
# I will keep you safe #
# 敞开你的心扉吧 #
# Open up all the world inside #
# 今夜你将精彩绽放 #
# So you come alive tonight #
# 我会一直守护着你 #
# I will keep you safe #
西域男孩的粉丝们是超棒的
You know the fans for Westlife have been amazing.
没法形容的
You know there's no other way to describe it.
他们就是我们在这里的原因 我们仍然站在这里的原因
Like, they're the reason we're here, obviously, the reason we're still here
他们和你一起沉浸在了这短短一个半小时的旅程中
They just get lost in the little journey with you for an hour and a half.
然后散场 这一切就结束了
And then they walk out and it's all over.
我们退场 回到正轨
We walk out and we just go back to our normal places.
这90分钟或者在舞台上的点点滴滴
Well, for that 90 minutes or whatever on the stage,
我想对每一个人来说 都是特别的
it's pretty special, I think, for everybody.
我不知道你们已经长大 你知道 作为某一个乐队或者歌手的一名粉丝
I don't know you grow up, you know as a fan of some band or music
这对于你们生活的影响
and you know the impact that that has on you as a person.
我从来没想过会对大家有这样的影响
But I just never expected to have that impact on people.
想到我们曾经在一些人生命中 扮演了一个重要角色 感觉有点奇怪
It's weird to think that we've been a big part of someone's life like that.
但是这却让我感到很骄傲
But it makes me feel proud to say that we have been.
提到这个也是 粉丝们会明白
Saying that too, like, fans have to realise
当我们站在音乐会的舞台上
when we are on stage on a concert tour,
我们十分享受台上的每一刻 那是最精彩的部分
we don't not enjoy any of that. That's the best part.
今晚 你看到的我们就是最精彩的时刻
Tonight if you're watching us now is the best part.
我并不想任何人结束这种悲伤
I don't want anybody to walk out of the last gig sad.
尽管我很伤心 他们也很伤心
Even though I'll be sad and they will be sad
但是 它将会是一个愉快的悲伤
but it's gotta be a happy sad.
是 我们一起走过14年
It gotta be, like, we've had 14 years, you know.
14年精彩的回忆 14年快乐的时光
It's 14 years of amazing memories. It's 14 years of amazingly good times.
带回家的只是那些快乐的时光 而不是那些悲伤的
And just go home remembering the good times, not the sad ones.
# 窈窕淑女 #
# Uptown girl #
# 她住在那高档的住宅区 #
# She's been living in her uptown world #
# 我赌她从没跟街头男孩交往过 #
# I bet she never had a back street guy #
# 我赌她妈妈也没跟她说过为什么不可 #
# I bet her mama never told her why #
# 我想交个窈窕淑女 窈窕淑女 #
# I'm gonna try for an uptown girl # Uptown girl #
# 她住在那高档的住宅区 #
# She's been living in her white bread world #
# 高档的住宅区 #
# White bread world #
# 只要是热血青年就有机会 热血青年就有机会 #
# As long as anyone with hot blood can # Hot blood can #
# 现在她来寻找乡村男孩 #
# And now she's looking for a downtown man #
# 乡村男孩 #
# Downtown man #
# 那就是我呀 #
# That's what I am #
一起来！
Come on!
# 日子一天天过去 她会明白 #
# And when she knows what she wants from her time #
# 她想要什么 #
# Wants from her time #
# 等她从梦中醒来 从梦中醒来 #
# And when she wakes up # She wakes up #
# 就会做好决定 #
# And makes up her mind #
# 她会发现我这人不错 #
# She'll see I'm not so tough #
# 因为我们相爱了 #
# just because I'm in love #
# 和一个窈窕淑女 窈窕淑女 #
# With an uptown girl # Uptown girl #
# 我在她的窈窕世界看见过她 #
# You know I've seen her in her uptown world #
# 窈窕世界 #
# Uptown world #
# 看得出她已经玩腻了她的高档玩具 #
# She's getting tired of her high class toys #
# 高档玩具 #
# High class toys #
# 还有那些富家公子送她的高档礼物 #
# And all her presents from her uptown boys #
# 高档玩具 #
# Uptown boys #
# 她现在有其他的选择了 #
# She's got a choice #
# 窈窕淑女 #
# Uptown girl #
# 你知道我没钱给你买珍珠首饰 #
# You know I can't afford to buy her pearls #
# 但搞不好哪天我的好运来了 #
# But maybe someday when my ship comes in #
# 她就会知道我是多么好的人 #
# She'll understand what kind of guy I've been #
# 多么好的人 #
# I've been #
# 那时我就成功了 #
# And then I'll win #
# 当她走在路上 #
# And when she's walking #
# 她看起来是那么婀娜 #
# She's looking so fine #
# 当她和别人聊天时 #
# And when she's talking #
# 她会说我们俩是一对 #
# She'll say that she's mine #
# 她会发现我这人不错 #
# She'll say I'm not so tough #
# 因为我们相爱了 #
# Just because I'm in love with an uptown girl #
# 她住在那高档的住宅区 #
# She's been living in her white bread world #
# 只要是热血青年就有机会 #
# As long as anyone with hot blood can #
# 现在她来寻找乡村男孩 #
# And now she's looking for a downtown man #
# 那就是我呀 #
# That's what I am #
# 窈窕淑女 窈窕淑女 #
# Uptown girl Uptown girl #
# 她是我的窈窕淑女 我的窈窕淑女 #
# She's my uptown girl   My uptown girl #
# 你知道我爱上了那个窈窕淑女 #
# You know I'm in love with an uptown girl #
# 窈窕淑女 #
# Uptown girl #
# 她是我的窈窕淑女 我的窈窕淑女 #
# She's my uptown girl  My uptown girl #
# 你知道我们相爱了 #
# You know I'm in love with an uptown girl #
# 我已爱上了她 #
# Going uptown #
# 她是我的窈窕淑女 #
# She's my uptown girl #
# 我已爱上了她 #
# Going uptown #
# 你知道我们相爱了 #
# You know I'm in love with an uptown girl #
# 我已爱上了她 #
# Going uptown #
# 我的窈窕淑女 #
# My uptown girl #
# 我已爱上了她 #
# Going uptown #
# 你知道我们相爱了 #
# You know I'm in love with an uptown girl #
# 女孩 女孩 女孩 … #
# Girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl #
# 窈窕淑女 淑女 淑女 淑女 … #
# Uptown girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl #
# 女孩 女孩 女孩 … #
# Girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl #
# 淑女 淑女 淑女 … #
# 日复一日 时光流逝 #
# Day after day, time passed away #
# 我只是无法忘记你 #
# Yeah, and I just can't get you off my mind #
# 没人知道 我将思念深藏心底 #
# Nobody knows, I hide it inside #
# 我一直在尝试 但还是找不到 #
# I keep on searching, but I can't find #
# 找不到勇气让你知道 #
# Got the courage to show to letting you know #
# 我从未如此深爱过 #
# I've never felt so much love before #
# 所以再一次地 我想要 #
# And once again I'm thinking about #
# 找到解决的办法 #
# Taking the easy way out #
大家一起来!
You sing!
# 但是如果我让你离开 我永远无法知晓 #
# But if I let you go I will never know #
# 如果让你留在我身边 我的生活会如何 #
# What my life would be holding you close to me #
# 也无法看到你在我身后的微笑 #
# Will I ever see you smiling back at me? #
# 哦 是的 #
# Oh, yeah #
# 我怎么会知道 #
# How will I know #
# 如果我让你离开了 #
# If I let you go? #
# 一夜接着一夜 我听见自己的心声 #
# Night after night, I hear myself say #
# 为何这种感觉无法消退 #
# Why can't this feeling just fade away #
# 没有人像你一样 #
# There's no one like you #
# 和我心灵相通 #
# You speak to my heart #
# 为何我们不在一个世界 #
# It's such a shame we're worlds apart #
# 我太害羞而难于启齿 又太骄傲害怕失去 #
# I'm too shy to ask, I'm too proud to lose #
# 但是迟早 我要做出选择 #
# But sooner or later I gotta choose #
# 我再次想要 #
# And once again I'm thinking about #
# 找到解决的办法 #
# Taking the easy way out #
# 但是如果让你离开 我将无法知晓 #
# But if I let you go I will never know #
# 如果让你留在身边 我的生活将会怎样 #
# What my life would be holding you close to me #
# 也无法看到你在我身后的微笑 #
# Will I ever see you smiling back at me? #
# 哦 是的 #
# Oh, yeah #
# 我怎么会知道 #
# How will I know #
# 如果我让你离开了 #
# If I let you go? #
# 我再次想要 #
# And once again I'm thinking about #
# 找到解决的办法 #
# Taking the easy way out #
大家一起来!
You sing!
# 但是如果让你离开 我将无法知晓 #
# But if I let you go I will never know #
# 如果让你留在身边 我的生活将会怎样 #
# What my life would be holding you close to me #
# 留在我身边 #
# Close to me, yeah #
# 也无法看到你在我身后的微笑 #
# Will I ever see you smiling back at me? #
# 看到你在我身后的微笑 哦 是的
# See you smiling back at me #
FILAN: Oh, yeah #
# 我怎么会知道 #
# How will I know #
# 如果我让你离开了 #
# If I let you go? #
# 与你站在我们两人的秘密花园 #
# So here we stand in our secret place #
# 闹市的声音远去 #
# Where the sound of the crowd is so far away #
# 你拉起我的手 带给我家的温暖 #
# And you take my hand and it feels like home #
# 我们都明白我们属于彼此 #
# We both understand it's where we belong #
# 我该怎么说 怎么说出再见 #
# So how do I say, do I say goodbye? #
# 我们都有梦想 我们都想要展翅高飞 #
# We both have our dreams, we both wanna fly #
# 就让这个夜晚 抚慰你我 #
# So let's take tonight to carry us through #
# 每个孤寂的时光 #
# The lonely times #
# 当我离开时 一定会回头深望着你 #
# I'll always look back as I walk away #
# 这份记忆会永远深藏我心 #
# This memory will last for eternity #
# 别离的伤心眼泪终究会在雨中消失 #
# And all of our tears will be lost in the rain #
# 直到我循着记忆的轨迹 回到你的怀抱 #
# Till I find my way back to your arms again #
# 但直到那一天 你会知道你是 #
# But until that day you know you are #
# 我心中的女王 #
# The queen of my heart #
# 在我心上 #
# My heart #
# 所以紧紧拥抱今晚吧 千万不要放手 #
# So let's take tonight and never let go #
# 利用这支舞 与你像是没有明天似的拥吻着 #
# While dancing we'll kiss like there's no tomorrow #
# 所有的星星像钻石戒指一样闪耀 #
# As the stars sparkle down like a diamond ring #
# 我要珍藏这一刻 直到我们再次相见 #
# I'll treasure this moment till we meet again #
# 但是不管多远 不管有多远
# But no matter how far #
No matter how far #
# 或者你可能在哪里 你可能在哪里
# Or where you may be #
Where you may be #
# 我只要闭上双眼 只要闭上双眼
# I just close my eyes #
just close my eyes #
# 你就会出现在我梦里 #
# And you're in my dreams #
# 请在那儿等候着我 直到我们再次相见 #
# And there you will be until we meet #
跟我一起唱,Croke Park!
# Sing with me, Croke Park! #
# 我会回头深望着你 哦 是的
# I'll always look back #
Oh, yeah #
# 在我离开的时候 在我离开的时候
# As I walk away #
As I walk away #
这份记忆会永远深藏我心
# This memory will last #
Will last #
# 永远 永远 #
# For eternity  For eternity #
# 别离的伤心眼泪终究会在雨中消失 #
# And all off our tears will be lost in the rain #
# 直到我循着记忆的轨迹 回到你的怀抱 #
# Till I find my way back to your arms again #
# 但是直到那一天,你会知道你是 #
# But until that day you know you are #
# 我心中的女王 #
# The queen of my heart #
# 每个人跟我们一起唱最后的节奏 #
# Each and every one of you sing this last bit with us.#
# 当我离开时 一定会回头深望着你 #
# I'll always look back as I walk away #
# 我离开的时候 #
# As I walk away #
# 这份记忆会永远深藏我心 #
# This memory will last  It's gonna last #
# 永远 永远 #
# For eternity  For eternity #
# 我别离的伤心眼泪终究会在雨中消失 #
# And all off our tears will be lost in the rain #
# 直到我循着记忆的轨迹 回到你的怀抱 #
# Till I find my way back to your arms again #
# 你的怀抱 #
# Your arms again #
# 但是直到那一天 你会知道你是 #
# But until that day you know you are #
# 我心中的女王 #
# The queen of my heart #
# 哦 是的 #
# Oh, yeah #
# 你是我心中的女王 我心中的女王 #
# You're the queen of my heart  Queen of my heart #
# 不过多少年过去 我心中的女王 #
# No matter how many years it takes  Queen of my heart #
# 我会把所有奉献给你 #
# I'll give it all to you Oh, yeah, yeah #
# 我心中的女王 #
# Queen of my heart #
# The queen of my heart #
Dublin 各位今晚过得如何
Dublin, how are you feeling tonight?
棒极了 看起来是...
It's amazing. It looks...
是我这辈子见过的最大的演唱会
It's like the biggest hen party I've ever seen in my life.
我想在这一刻在电影院里向所有人问好
I'd like at this point to say hello to everybody in the cinemas
他们吃着爆米花 喝着饮料
that's eating their popcorn and drinking their drinks.
希望你享受在欧洲的时光
I hope your enjoying it around Europe.
我愿意给你来自爱尔兰最热烈的欢迎
And I'd like to give you a big welcome from Ireland.
很高兴太阳及时出来了
And I'm glad the sunshine came out just in time.
数到三 Ireland
So, on count of three, Ireland
冲在欧洲的每个人大吼 1 2 3
give everybody in Europe a big shout out. One, two, three!
我们可能没有赢得欧洲冠军
We may not have won the European championships
但是我们知道怎么举办一场盛大的演唱会 不是吗 Dublin?
but we know how to have a party, don't we, Dublin?
还有你知道吗 这些五彩斑斓的雨衣
And you know what, all the different colour raincoats
从我站的地方看过去 是演唱会美丽的一抹色彩
from where I'm standing, it just adds to it.
超炫
It just looks fantastic.
所以 无论如何...
So, anyway...
噢嘞 噢嘞 噢嘞
Ole, ole, ole.
没有欢呼的感觉 嗯?
There's nothing like a bit of ole, ole, ole, eh?
一般这时候我们会读出横幅上的标语
What we usually do at this time is read out the banners.
14年了
Nam over the 14 years
横幅的字都有些模糊了
some of the banners have got increasingly filthy.
老实说 我们还曾好笑地调侃过这些横幅
And we've been pleasantly disgusted, I have to tell you.
我无法把所有的横幅读出来 但是我会读出一部分 好吧?
Nam I can't read them all, but I'm gonna shout a few, OK?
"西域男孩 与我同在"
"Stick it in me, Westlife."
"后街男孩 你们最后的一个赛季"
"BSB, you're so last season."
"感谢西域男孩 这14年的精彩"
"Thank you, Westlife, for 14 amazing years."
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
"尼基 你超给力 我也会挺你的"
"Nicky, hit me with your real thing and I'll raise you up."
我猜你是指那首歌 对吗?
I presume you mean the song, right?
"西城男孩 今天是我们的周年纪念日 这份记忆将永远珍藏在我心里"
"Westlife, today is our anniversary. This memory will last an eternity"
棒极了 棒极了
Brilliant. Brilliant.
你们很拿手那些歌词的韵律嘞
Enough with the rhymes, get naked already.
前面有很多国旗 德国的 还有荷兰的
There are a lot of flags in the front. We'l/e got German y, we'l/e got Holland.
还有捷克的歌迷 爱尔兰的歌迷
We've got the Czech Republic, we've got Ireland.
我们还有来自挪威 丹麦 以色列 英国和瑞典的歌迷
We've got Norway, Denmark, Israel, England, Sweden.
今晚大家相聚一处 嗯?
You're all here tonight for a party, eh?
我没法全部读完 你想读出它们吗?
I can't read them all. Do you want to read them?
你们可以选一个出来吗?
Can you pick one out?
"西城男孩 所有委内瑞拉的歌迷爱你们 支持你们"
"Westlife, all fans from Venezuela love and support you."
"再会 我们与你们每个人同在"
"We will always be with you, each, with this farewell."
谢谢你们 委内瑞拉的歌迷 - 谢谢你们 委内瑞拉的歌迷
- Thank you, Venezuela. - Thank you, Venezuela.
你们知道我们接下来会做什么吗?最后一次 我们一起站在中央
# Do you know what we're gonna do, lads? One last time, stand in the middle here.#
过来 我们四个挨得近一点
Come here. Can we all fit on the... the four of us...
现在把你们的相机拿出来 照一张最后的合影
Let's get your cameras out and take one picture for the last time.
我数到三 我要你们一起打开闪关灯照相
On the count of three, I want you all to flash at us.
不 用你们的相机
No, with your cameras.
太冷了 好了 开始啦 1 2 3
It's too cold. All right, here we go. One, two, three.
你知道吗,这太酷了
Do you know what, that was so cool.
我们要换个姿势了 你们准备好了吗?
We're gonna do another one. Are you ready?
非常谢谢 Dublin 我们继续表演吧
Thank you very much, Dublin, let's move on with the show.
看 在下面的那个
See that one down there?
那是一句斯莱戈谚语 说得是... - 我们在相机里头
- That's a Sligo phrase. It says... - We're live on camera.
是的 上面写的是 反对我 - 不...不是你想得那样
I Yeah, it says, Buck me
- Not... Not what you think.
她是...她是个作家
She's... She's an author.
不管怎样 我们下面要唱的这首歌
Anyway, the next song we're gonna do
来自我们几年前发行的唱片 唱片名字是纯真年代
is from an album we recorded a few years ago called Allow Us To Be Frank.
这是为今晚在这儿的老顽童准备的
And it's for all the old fogies here tonight.
我们这有人头发已经灰白了吗?
Anybody here with grey hair
我们这儿谁的头发已经发白了后来又染色了的 举起手来
Anyone here with grey hair and the y dyed it. Stick your hands up.
好了 我希望你们不会晕头转向
Well, I hope it doesn't run in the rain.
这首歌的名字是 晕头转向
This is called Ain't That A Kick In The Head?
我们开始吧!
Here we go!
# 嘿! #
# Hey!#
# 一个人能有多幸运? #
# How lucky can one guy be? #
# 我吻了她 她吻了我 #
# I kissed her and she kissed me #
# 就像那个小伙子曾经说的 难道没有感觉 #
# Like the fella once said,"Ain't that a kick..."#
# 晕头转向吗 #
# CROWD: "...in the head?"#
# 这个房间是全黑色 #
# The room was completely black #
# 我抱住她 她抱住我 #
# I hugged her and she hugged back #
# 就像水手说的 难道没有感觉到晕头转向吗 #
# Like the sailor said, quote,"Ain't that a hole in the boat?"#
# 我的头一直晕晕的 #
# My head keeps spinnin' #
# 我要去睡觉 保持着这种眩晕的感觉 #
# I go to sleep and keep grinnin' #
# 如果这只是开始 #
# If this is just the beginnin' #
# 我的人生将会变得多么美妙 #
# My life is gonna be beautiful #
# 我已经接受了足够多的阳光用来传播 #
# I've sunshine enough to spread #
# 就像那个小伙子说的 #
# It's just like the fella said #
# 快点告诉我 难道不是爱让我感觉到晕头转向吗 #
# "Tell me quick, ain't love a kick in the head?"#
# 嘿! #
# Hey!#
# 就像那个小伙子曾说的 难道没有感觉到晕头转向吗 #
# Like the fella once said,"Ain't that a kick in the head?"#
# 就像水手说的 难道没有感觉到晕头转向吗 #
# Like the sailor said, quote,"Ain't that a hole in the boat?"#
# 我的脑袋一直晕晕的 #
# My head keeps spinnin' #
# 我要去睡觉 保持这种眩晕的感觉 #
# I go to sleep and keep grinnin' #
# 如果这只是开始 #
# If this is just the beginnin' #
# 我的人生将会变得多么美妙 #
# My life is gonna be beautiful #
# 她告诉我 我们将会结婚 #
# She is tellin' me we'll be wed #
# 她挑了一张超大尺寸的大床 #
# She's picked out a king- size bed #
# 我感觉非常好 否则我就是生病了 #
# I couldn't feel any better or I would be sick #
# 嘿! #
# Hey!#
# 快点告诉我 难道没有感觉到晕头转向吗 #
# Tell me quick, oh, ain't love a kick? #
# 快点告诉我 难道没有感觉到 #
# Tell me quick  Ain't love a kick #
# 晕头转向吗 #
# In the head? #
# 嘿!嘿! #
# Hey! Hey!#
对未来的恐惧 巨大的恐惧
Hugely scared of the future, hugely scared.
我担心着两件事 一件事是这次演唱会的晚上
Two things I'm worried about. One is the immediate night of the show
明天早上你们会有何感触
and how you feel the next morning.
然后我有点担心一年 两年或者三年后 我会有何感触
And then I kinda fear a year or two or three down the road how will I feel?
因为毫无疑问我们会怀念我们曾经的过往
Because there's no doubt about it we're gonna miss it.
你知道 我们四个人真的是最好的朋友
You know, we genuinely have been the best of friends
在整个歌唱生涯
throughout this whole process.
我人生中的美妙夜晚
Some of the best nights I've ever had in my life
都是和西城男孩里的这些人一起度过的
have been with the guys in Westlife, you know.
包括发唱片 在舞台上表演
Making records, you know, standing on stage in front of audiences,
一起听录制的唱片
you know, listening back to songs that we've recorded,
那时候我们东奔西跑的
that's the buzz, you know.
那些日子是我生命中最美好的一页
That's what was always the best part for me.
我不敢去想这次演唱会结束后的那个星期会如何
I'm not looking forward for the week after Croke Park,
我可以告诉你这么多
I can tell you that much.
将会发生很大的改变 对我们所有人来讲都是巨大的 巨大的改变
It's gonna be a big change. Massive, massive change for all of us.
我是指 我甚至没有想过怎么开始
# I mean, I don't even have a notion how I am gonna begin
进入我人生的下一个篇章
to move on to the next chapter of my life,
但是 我觉得我们都已经做好准备了
but, you know, I think we've made our minds up
我将会用一种积极的心态继续前行
and I'm gonna, you know, move forward with a positive mental attitude.
而且你知道 你只会记住那些伟大的时刻
And you just remember the great moments, you know.
# 我有种感觉 哇哦 #
# I gott a feeling  Whoo-hoo #
# 今晚会是一个美好的晚上 #
# Tonight's gonna be a good night #
# 今晚会是一个美好的 美好的晚上 #
# Tonight's gonna be a good, good night #
# 有种感觉 哇哦 #
# A feeling  Whoo- hoo#
# 今晚会是一个美好的晚上 #
# That tonight's gonna be a good night #
# 今晚会是一个美好的 美好的晚上 #
# That tonight's gonna be a good, good night #
# 有种感觉 哇哦 #
# A feeling  Whoo- hoo #
## 今晚会是一个美好的晚上 #
# That tonight's gonna be a good night #
# 今晚会是一个美好的 美好的晚上 #
# That tonight's gonna be a good, good night #
# 有种感觉 哇哦 #
# A feeling  Whoo-hoo #
# 今晚会是一个美好的晚上 #
# That tonight's gonna be a good night #
你们准备好了吗 Croke Park?
Are you ready, Croke Park?
让我看见你们跳起来 跳起来 跳起来
Let's see you jump, jump, jump
# 我们来了 开始啦 我们要摇摆起来 #
# Here we come, here we go, we gotta rock #
# 摇摆 摇摆 摇摆 摇摆 摇摆 #
# Rock, rock, rock, rock, rock #
# 好聚好散 现在我们嗨翻了 #
# Easy come, easy go, now we on top #
# 嗨翻 嗨翻了 嗨翻了 嗨翻了 嗨翻了 #
# Top, top, top, TOP, TOP #
# 感受着节拍 摇摆身体 摇摆起来 不要停 #
# Feel the shot, body rock, rock it, don't stop #
# 停 停 停 停 停 #
# Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop #
# 转啊转 跳啊跳 昼夜不停地跳 #
# Round and round, up and down, around the clock #
# 时钟 时钟 时钟 时钟 时钟 #
# Clock, clock, clock, clock, clock #
# 我知道我们会有一场舞会 #
# I know that we'll have a ball #
# 如果我们下去 然后出门 什么都不管 #
# If we get down and go out and just lose it all #
# 我觉得压力好大 我想放松 #
# I feel stressed out, I wanna let it go #
# 所以让我们出门去 打破所有束缚 #
# Let's go way out spaced out and losing all control #
# 给我满上杯 #
# Fill up my cup, mazel tov #
# 看看她的舞蹈 快脱了吧 #
# Look at her dance, just take it off #
# 让我们尽情嗨吧 我们闹到让这个镇子关门 #
# Let's paint the town, we'll shut it down #
# 每天我都在搪塞 #
# Every day I'm shuffling #
# 我有种感觉 #
# I gotta feeling #
# 今晚会是一个美好的晚上 #
# Tonight's gonna be a good night #
# 今晚会是一个美好的 美好的晚上 #
# Tonight's gonna be a good, good night #
# 躺在你躺着的地方 #
# Lay where you're laying #
# 不要出声 #
# Don't make a sound #
# 我知道他们在看着 #
# I know they're watching #
# 他们在看着 #
# They're watching #
# 所有的骚动 #
# All the commotion #
# 小孩子喜欢玩耍 #
# The kiddie like play #
# 有人在说话 #
# Has people talking #
# 他们在谈论 #
# And they're talking #
# 你 #
# You #
# 你如火的性感 #
# Your sex is on fire #
# 让我着迷 #
# Consumed #
# 将会发生什么 #
# With what's to transpire #
# 小巷的黑暗 #
# The dark of the alley #
# 白昼的破碎 #
# The breaking of day #
# 我正驾驭的大脑 #
# The head while I'm driving #
# 我正驾驭的 #
# I'm driving #
# 张开绵软的嘴唇 #
# Soft lips are open #
# 苍白的指节 #
# Knuckles are pale #
# 看上去你好像快要死去了 #
# Feels like you're dying #
# 你快要死去了 #
# You're dying #
# 你 #
# You #
# 你如火的性感 #
# Your sex is on fire #
# 让我着迷 #
# Consumed #
# 将发生什么 #
# With what's to transpire #
# 你 #
# You #
# 你如火的性感 #
# Your sex is on fire #
# 让我着迷 #
# Consumed #
# 将会发生什么 #
# With what's to transpire #
# 你 #
# You #
# 你如火的性感 #
# Your sex is on fire #
# 让我着迷 #
# Consumed #
# 将会发生什么 #
# With what's to transpire #
快来！
Come on!
# 我知道你喜欢我 #
# I know you like me #
# 我知道 #
# I know you do #
# 这就是我总是出现在你身边的原因 #
# That's why whenever I come around #
# 我也知道你是愿意的 #
# She's all over you #
# 我知道你喜欢我 #
# I know you like me #
# 我知道 #
# I know you do #
# 这就是我总是出现在你身边的原因 #
# That's why whenever I come around #
# 我也知道你是愿意的 #
# She's all over you #
# 我知道你想要(跟我在一起) #
# I know you want it #
# 这个显而易见 #
# It's easy to see #
# 在你内心深处 #
# And in the back of your mind #
# 我知道我们会有一段美好时光 #
# I know you should be on with me #
# 不用期待你的男友像我一样热情 #
# Don't cha wish your boyfriend was hot like me? #
# 不用期待你的男友像我一样狂热 #
# Don't cha wish your boyfriend was a freak like me? #
# 不用 #
# Don't cha? #
# 不用期待你的男友像我一样癫狂 #
# Don't cha wish your boyfriend was wrong like me? #
# 不用期待你的男友像我一样风趣 #
# Don't cha wish your boyfriend was fun like me? #
# 不用 #
# Don't cha? #
# 内心挣扎 #
# fight the feeling #
# 静一下好了 #
# Or leave it alone #
# Leave it alone #
# 因为如果这并不是爱 那就不足以 #
# 'Cause if it ain't love, it just ain't enough #
# 成就幸福的家 #
# To leave a happy home #
# 我们还是做朋友吧 #
# Let's keep it friendly #
# 你必须遵守规则 #
# You have to play fair #
# 看吧 我不在乎 #
# See, I don't care #
# 但我知道她做不到 #
# But I know he ain't gon' wanna share #
# 不用期待你的男友像我一样热情 #
# Don't cha wish your boyfriend was hot like me? #
# 不用期待你的男友像我一样狂热 #
# Don't cha wish your boyfriend was a freak like me? #
# 不用 #
# Don't cha? #
# 不用期待你的男友像我一样癫狂 #
# Don't cha wish your boyfriend was wrong like me? #
# 不用期待你的男友像我一样风趣 #
# Don't cha wish your boyfriend was fun like me? #
# 风趣 #
# Big fun #
# 不用 #
# Don't cha? #
# 我知道谁在你心里 #
# I know who's on your mind #
# 我知道我们有一段美好时光 #
# I know we'd have a good time #
# 我们是好奇的 我们是畏怯的 #
# We're fresh, we're funky #
Croke Park 尖叫吧
Croke Park, scream!
好了 Croke Park 到时间了
All right Croke Park, this is the time now
我们要变得有些疯狂了
where we're gonna go a little bit crazy.
你们准备好要疯狂了吗?
Is Croke Park ready to go crazy?
# 跳 跳 #
# Jump! Jump! #
# 跳 跳 跳 #
# Jump! Jump! Jump! #
# 不用期待你的男友热情 热情 热情 热情 热情 热情 #
# Don't cha wish your boyfriend was hot, hot, hot, hot #
# 热情 热情 热情 热情 热情 热情 #
# hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot #
# 不用 #
# Don't cha? #
# 不用期待你的男友热情 热情 热情 热情 热情 热情 #
# Don't cha wish your boyfriend was hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot #
# 热情、热情、热情、热情、热情、热情、热情 #
# hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot #
# 不用 #
# Don't cha? #
# 不用期待你的男友热情 热情 热情 热情 热情 热情 #
# Don't cha wish your boyfriend was hot, hot, hot, hot, hot #
# 不用 不用 不用 不用 #
# Don't cha, don't cha, don't cha, don't cha? #
# 地狱不再,现在这里是天堂 #
# Hell is gone, now heaven's here #
# 这里没什么让你害怕的 #
# There's nothing left for you to fear #
# 边摇摆你的臀部边走过来 #
# Shake your ass come over here #
# Dublin 尖叫吧 #
# Dublin, scream #
# 我是一座燃烧的雕像 它象征着我以前的所有 #
# I'm a burning effigy of everything I used to be #
# 你能理解我岩石般的内心 亲爱的 #
# You're my rock of empathy, my dear #
# 让我招待你 #
# Let me entertain you #
# 来吧 跳起来 跳起来 #
# Come on, jump, jump! #
# 让我招待你 #
# Let me entertain you #
# 生命太过短暂 死去未免可惜 #
# Life's too short for you to die #
# 为你自己找个理由 #
# Grab yourself an alibi #
# 天知道你妈妈是个撒谎的人 #
# Heaven knows your mother lied man cher #
# 把你做的对的事从错误的事中找出来 #
# Separate your right from wrongs #
# 来吧 唱首不一样的歌 #
# Come and sing a different song #
# 壶里烧着水所以不会太久 #
# The kettle's on so don't be long, man cher #
# 让我招待你 #
# Let me entertain you #
# 快来 快来 快来 快来 #
# Come on, come on, come on, come on #
# 让我招待你 #
# Let me entertain you #
# 再来一次 #
One more time!
# 让我招待你 #
# Let me entertain you #
# 妈妈 刚杀了个人 #
# Mama, just killed a man #
# 拿枪抵着他的头 #
# Put a gun against his head #
# 扣动我的扳机 现在他已经死了 #
# Pulled my trigger, now he's dead #
# 妈妈 人生才刚刚开始 #
# Mama, life has just begun #
# 但是现在我却把它完全毁掉了 #
# But now I've gone and thrown it all away #
# 妈妈 呜呜呜 #
# Mama, ooh #
# 本不想让你哭泣 #
# Didn't mean to make you cry #
# 如果我明天这个时候没回来 #
# If I'm not back again this time tomorrow #
# 撑住 撑住 就好像一切都没什么大不了的 #
# Carry on, carry on, as if nothing really matters #
# 让我们听奇恩唱 #
Let's hear it for Kian, everybody!
# 你以为你可以用石头砸我 向我眼里吐口水? #
# So you think you can stop me and spit in my eye #
# 你以为你可以既爱我又让我去死? #
# So you think you can love me and leave me to die #
# 哦 宝贝 #
# Oh, baby #
# 你不能这样对我 宝贝 #
# Can't do this to me, baby #
# 我只是想离开 只是想马上离开这儿 #
# just gotta get out just gotta get right outta here #
# 哦 是的 #
# Ooh, yeah #
# Ooh, yeah, ooh #
# 没什么大不了的 #
# Nothing really matters #
# 你可以看见 #
# Europe, you can see #
# 没什么大不了的 #
# Nothing really matters #
# 对我来说没什么事是重要的 #
# Nothing really matters to me #
# 无论风怎么吹 #
# Any way the wind blows #
整个经历里
The whole experience,
我是指没有人会理解 或者曾经理解这段歌唱生涯 首先我们四个人
nobody will ever, ever understand it I mean, the four of us, first of all.
你怎么解释这14年?
How do you explain 14 years?
这好像 不可能解释的清楚
It's like, it's impossible to do,
但这完完全全把我们的生活向好的方面改变了
but it's completely changed our lives for the good.
只是我 不懂摇滚
But just, I don't know rock and roll.
就像我们真的非常非常享受这一切
Like, we did enjoy ourselves very, very much.
但是 你懂的 我们也许只是一个男孩乐队 但是我们享受这一切
nd, you know, we might be a boy band but we had a lot of fun.
假如有一天早上你醒来的时候
I suppose you wake up one morning
你发现你手里拿着梦想成真的门票
and you realise you're sitting in the biggest dream come true ticket
那是未曾有过的事情 你能理解
that's ever been written, you know.
那就像有人在我17岁的时候给我写了一封信
It's like somebody wrote me a letter when I was 17
上面写着 你将环游世界10次
and going,"You're gonna travel the world 10 times over,
你会卖出4500万张唱片 你会碰到你心爱的人
"you're gonna sell 45 million records, you're gonna meet the love of your life.
你将会有很多很多的钱
"You're gonna have...make lots of money
永远都不会为钱发愁
"and hopefully never have money troubles again
然后 快乐地度过余生
"and live the rest of your life as happy as possible."
是这样 就是这样 这就是所发生的事情
That's... That's it. That's what happened.
我过去经常在一些专辑上写"感谢活在梦中"
I used to always write on some of the album thank yous"Live the dream."
我想 我不知道从哪听到的这个说法
And I think... I don't know where I got the saying from,
我一直感觉我们活在梦里
but I always felt that we were living the dream, you know.
每个人的梦各不相同 但是我们四个...
Everybody's dream is different, but the four of us,
当然 我把Brain也包括在内
and I'll include Brian into that obviously, as well.
这就是我们想要的的
You know, that's what we wanted.
我们一直都想成为明星
You know, we always wanted to be famous pop stars.
同样忘掉你们也是很难做到的
FILAN: It's very hard to forget the audience as well,
忘记演唱会 忘记那种尖叫疯狂的感觉
forget the concerts, forget that feeling of the screams, the loudness,
以及当你走下舞台时耳中的欢呼
the ringing in your ears when we get off the stage
还有那种每晚走上舞台时的激动之情
and, you know, that whole buzz of walking into the stage every night.
在你走出去的前10秒 你感觉你...
The first 10 seconds before you come on, you just feel like you're...
真的很难去描述
It's hard to describe it.
就是在你即将上台看到如此多观众之前的10秒钟
It's just that you have that 10 seconds of the crowd your about to see
你知道那将会很疯狂 而且他们也同样为你而疯狂
and you know it's going to be exciting and you know they're excited for you.
你永远都不会忘记 那是将伴随你一生
You'll never forget that. It's one of those things that live with you forever.
# 当你看起来如此令人窒息 #
# When you're looking like that #
# When you're looking like that that that #
# 我说 YEAH YEAH #
# I say, yeah, yeah #
# 她 5'7寸高 穿着紧身衣 小鹿般的眼睛 #
# She's a 5'70"in catsuit and Bambi eyes #
# 令每个盯着她看的人 无法相信他是我的女孩 #
# Everybody who's staring wouldn't believe that the girl was mine #
# 我早该知道我犯了错误 #
# I should have known I was wrong #
# 当我不舍的离开它的生活 #
# When I left her for a life in pity #
# 他们说要等你失去时才会懂得思念 #
# But the y say you never miss the water until it's gone #
# 看来我爱你的方式很失败 #
# Guess I failed to love you #
# 而今晚你已经把爱全部带走 #
# You're taking it out tonight #
来吧
Come on!
# 我该怎么让你离开 #
# How am I supposed to leave you now #
# 当你看起来如此令人窒息 #
# When you're looking like that? #
# 我不敢相信我竟然让你离开 #
# I can't believe what [just gave away #
# 现在我再也换不回你的心 #
# Now I can't take it back #
# 我不想从此迷失 迷失 #
# I don't wanna get lost # Lost #
# 我不愿过没有你的生活 #
# I don't wanna live my life without you #
# 我该怎么让你离开 #
# How am I supposed to leave you now #
# 当你看起来如此令人窒息 #
# When you're looking like that? #
# 她打扮的光芒四射 #
# She's all dressed up for glamour and rock and roll #
# 多想一把抱住她 离开这地方 #
# Wanna squeeze her real tight, get out of this place #
# 只要我能控制我自己 #
# If only I could take control #
# 但是她已经离我而去 #
# But she # 3 out of my reach forever #
# 但是一周之前她还躺在我身边 #
# And just a week ago she lied next to me #
# 就这样失去她是多么的讽刺 #
# It's so ironic how I had to lose just to see #
# 终于看清我爱你的方式多么失败 #
# that I failed to love you #
# 你今晚已将所有的爱带走 #
# And you're taking it out tonight #
# 我怎么能让你离开 #
# How am I supposed to leave you now #
# 当你看起来如此令人窒息 #
# When you're looking like that? #
# 我不敢相信我竟然让你离开 #
# I can't believe what I just gave away #
# 现在我再也换不回你的心 #
# Now I can't take it back #
# 我不想从此迷失 迷失 #
# I don't wanna get lost # Lost #
# 我不愿过没有你的生活 #
# I don't wanna live my life without you #
# 我怎么能让你离开 #
# How am I supposed to leave you now #
# 当你看起来如此令人窒息 #
# When you're looking like that? #
# 我永远不会忘记你 宝贝 #
# I don't wanna forget you, baby #
# 我不会去试着忘记 #
# I don't even wanna try #
# 我该如何走过你身边 #
# How am I supposed to walk on by #
# 当你看起来如此令人窒息 #
# When you're looking like that? #
# 我怎么能让你离开 #
# How am I supposed to leave you? #
# 当你看起来如此令人窒息 #
# When you're looking like that? #
# 我不相信我已经让你离开 #
# I can't believe what I just gave away #
# OH OH 宝贝 #
FILAN: # Oh, no, babe #
# 现在我再也换不回你的心 我迷失了 #
ALL: # 'Cause I can't take it back, I'm lost #
# 我不愿过没有你的生活 #
# I don't wanna live my life without you #
# 过没有你的生活 #
# Live my life without you #
# 我怎么能让你离开 #
# How am I supposed to leave you now #
# 当你看起来如此令人窒息 #
# When you're looking like that? #
# 我怎么能让你离开 #
# How am I supposed to leave you now #
# 当你看起来如此令人窒息 #
# When you're looking like that? #
# 我不相信我已经让你离开 #
# I can't believe what I just gave away #
# 现在我再也换不回你的心 #
# Now I can't take it back #
# 我不想从此迷失 迷失 #
# I don't wanna get lost # Lost #
# 我不愿过没有你的生活 #
# I don't wanna live my life without you #
# 我怎么能让你离开 #
# How am I supposed to leave you now #
# 当你看起来如此令人窒息 #
# When you're looking like that? #
# When you're looking like that #
# 当你看起来如此令人窒息 #
Croke Park 感觉如何?
Croke Park, how are you feeling?
OH 你们今晚真的棒极了 我必须说
Oh, you're looking mighty fine, this evening, I must say.
来到这 看到你们 实话实说 真的太疯狂了
To look out there and see all you guys, honestly, it's crazy.
当然不是因为天气 外面下雨了
Not to state the obvious, but I notice it's raining out there.
现在 我想知道 你们现在感觉好吗?
So, what I want to know is how do you feel about the idea
我们走出来 同你们一起淋雨
of us coming out there and getting wet with you?
好的
0K.
小伙伴们！14年了 西城男孩的粉丝们一直支持着我们
Guys, for 14 years the Westlife fans have supported us.
我想说 没有你们
I think it's fair to say like no other fan base-
我们不可能实现我们的梦想
You've made our dreams come true.
没下雨了
It's not raining.
等一下 我们想站到前面去
0/5 hang on a second, we just wanted to get out the front here
好了 来吧
Al! rig/lli guys-
这场表演让你们中的每一个人都沉浸其中
This show is dedicated to each and every one of you
是你们 让我们梦想成真
who have made our dreams come true.
小伙伴们
Hello.
我们爱你们 我们的粉丝对于我们意味着全世界
We love you so much. Our fans mean the world to us.
你们从来 也永远不会离开我们
You've never, ever, ever stopped supporting us.
我们生涯中所做的每一件事...
Every little thing we have ever done in our career,
都有你们支持我们 非常感谢！
you guys have been there for us. Thank you so much for that.
下面的一首歌曲...
The next song we're gonna do
是我们很久前的一个年度唱片
was the Record of the Year for us a long time ago
说到年度唱片 感谢你们所有人
and I would like to thank you all for making this Record of the Year
感谢你们的投票
and for every time you've voted for us,
感谢你们购买的我们的单曲 购买我们的专辑
for every single that you've bought, for every album you've bought,
感谢你们购买我们的门票
for every ticket you've bought.
真的 我们很爱很爱你们
Honestly, we love you so much.
来到你们中间 感觉真的很好
It feels really good to be out here in the middle of you.
你们感觉怎么样 还好吗?
How are you feeling? All right?
后面的朋友你们好吗?
How are you feeling at the back?
女士们 你们好吗
OK lads, are you ready?
接下来是年度唱片 名叫Mandy
As I said this is Record of the Year and this is called Mandy.
来吧
Hello!
# 回首往事 #
# I remember all my life #
# 凄风冷雨 #
# Raining down as cold as ice #
# 孤单的身影 #
# Shadows of a man #
# 凝神窗外 黑暗中的泪水与夜色一同滑落 #
# A face through a window cryin' in the night #
# 黎明又是新的一天 #
# The night goes into morning #
# 又是新的一天 #
# just another day #
# 快乐的人们掠过眼前 #
# Happy people pass my way #
# 那些眼神,唤起回忆 #
# Looking in their eyes I see a memory #
# 从未发现,你曾是我快乐的源泉 #
# I never realised how happy you made me #
# 你为我付出 不求索取 #
# You came and you gave without taking #
# 但我却让你离开 #
# But I sent you away #
# 你给我温暖 让我不再颤抖 #
# You kissed me and stopped me from shaking #
# 我需要你 #
# 'Cause I need you today #
# 回首往事 #
# I'm standing on the edge of time #
# 当爱在身边 我却走远 #
# I've walked away when love was blind #
# 去追寻征服的世界 #
# Caught up in a whirl of uphill climbing #
# 如今泪湿胸膛 生活曲不成调 #
# Tears are on my mind and not/lin' is rhyming #
# 你为我付出 不求索取 #
# You came and you gave without taking #
# 但我却让你离开 #
# But I sent you away #
# 你给我温暖 让我不再颤抖 #
# You kissed me and stopped me from shaking #
# 我需要你 #
# And I need you today #
来吧,Croke Park,让我听听你的声音
Come on, Croke Park, let me hear you scream. #
# 昨日如梦 面对现实 #
# Yesterday's a dream I face the morning #
# 眼泪飘在风中 心仍在痛 #
# Crying on the breeze The pain is calling #
# 你为我付出 不求索取 #
# Well, you came and you gave without taking #
# 但我却让你离开 #
# But I sent you away #
# 你给我温暖 让我不再颤抖 #
# You kissed me and stopped me from shaking #
# 我需要你 #
# 'Cause I need you today #
# 你为我付出 不求索取 #
# You came and you gave without taking #
# 但我却让你离开 #
# But I sent you away #
# 你给我温暖 让我不再颤抖 #
# You kissed me and stopped me from shaking #
# 我需要你 #
# I need you #
# Mandy 请听我满心的忏悔 #
# Oh, Mandy, won't you listen to what I've got to say #
# 宝贝 你让我全部忘记 #
# Oh, baby, don't you let me throw it all away #
# Mandy 请听我满心的忏悔 #
# Oh, Mandy, won't you listen to what I've got to say #
# 我需要你 #
# 'Cause I need you today #
# OH爱尔兰 #
# Oh, Ireland #
嗨！
Hello.
OH 老天 Croke Park 感觉怎么样
Oh, my God. Croke Park, how are you feeling now?
雨停了 怎么这么幸运?有点不可置信
It stopped raining. What is the luck? It's just unbelievable.
爱尔兰人的幸运
The luck of the Irish, huh?
真的很神奇 这么多观众
It's just amazing, guys, to be in the middle of this crowd, looking out.
真的很难以置信
It's absolutely unbelievable.
感谢你们今晚到场的每一个人
Thank you very much to each and every one of you that came down here tonight.
今晚在场有8万5千
There's 85, 000 people in here tonight.
喔！
Whoo!
难以置信
It's unbelievable.
我们从昨晚一直在做什么
Guys, we've been doing something last night.
昨晚观众的观众都很热情
Last night was a loud crowd,
但不得不说 今晚是最嗨的一次
but we have to say, tonight is the loudest best ever...
我们从没在这么多人面前表演过 我是说
we've ever performed in front ofi and I mean that.
我们刚才在后台说起这个
We were just talking about it backstage
毫无疑问 这是我们所见过的最好的观众
that this is the best crowd we've ever had without a shadow of a doubt.
多么美好的一个夜晚啊 我们最后的表演
And what a night to have it, guys, our last show.
真的难以置信 非常感谢
It'kjust unbelievable Thank you so much-
好了 大家来玩人浪吧！
All right, guys, we're gonna get you to do a little Mexican wave for us now.
喔！
Whoo!
让大家再嗨一点
get everybody a bit more in the mood.
来吧,我们再从这边过去
So, what we're gonna do is we're gonna start over this side.
准备好了吗
Are you all right over there?
从前面一直到老后面
We're gonna start in the stands all the way around to this side
然后再返回来
and then everybody from the front all the way to the very back,
然后再到上面
and all the way up the top again
我们在中间
and we're gonna get in the middle of it, all right?
你们准备好了吗?
You've already done, man?
3 2 1 走你！
Right on three. One, two, three, go!
来点声音 Dublin 来点声音
You gotta make some noise. Dublin, make some noise.
跺脚 一起来 跺脚 来吧
Stamp your feet, everybody. Stamp your feet, let? go!
我们在Hogan stand
We're in the Hogan stand!
在哪?
FEEHILY: Where is it?
前面的朋友 准备好了吗?一 二 三 GO
FILAN: Everybody in the front ready? One, two, three. Go!
走一个
FEEHILY: Go!
上面！喔
- All at the top! - Whoo!
给自己鼓掌吧 Dublin
Give yourselves a round of applause, Dublin.
好了 小伙伴们 下一首歌
All right, guys, the next song we're gonna do
对我们四个人意义非凡
is a very special song for the four of us.
是我们听的第一首歌之一
It's one of the first songs we heard
使我们第一次去伦敦的时候
when we tripped out to London for the first time.
那真的很让人兴奋,这首歌永远改变了我们的生活
It was absolutely amazing. This song changed our life forever.
它是在我们心中是第一位的,所以你知道是什么
It was our first number one, so you definitely know the words to this.
在爱尔兰连续五周排名第一
It was number one for five weeks in Ireland.
# 我想知道 #
# I wanna know #
# 是谁告诉你我将离去 #
# Who ever told you I was letting go #
# 离开我生命中唯一的喜悦 #
# Of the only joy that I have ever known #
一起来
You sing.
# 女孩 他们都在说谎 #
CROWD: # Girl, they were lying #
# 看看四周 #
# just look around #
# 我们所熟知的那些人们 #
# And all of the people that we used to know #
# 都纷纷放弃 想要放手 #
# Ha ve just given up, the y wanna let it go #
# 但我们仍一直努力 #
# But we're still trying #
# 你应该知道我们之间的爱 是注定不会凋谢 #
# So you should know this love we share was never made to die #
# 我很开心跟你走在这条不回头的路上,我和你 #
# I'm glad we're on this one way street, just you and I #
一起来
Sing it.
# 我和你 #
# just you and I #
我永远不会与你说再见
I'm never gonna say goodbye #
# 因为我永远不想见到你哭泣 #
# 'Cause I never wanna see you cry #
# 我向你发誓 我的爱将直到永远 #
# I swore to you my love would remain #
# 我将爱你不渝 #
# And I swear it all over again and I #
# 我将永远不会伤害你 #
# I'm never gonna treat you bad #
# 我永远不愿见到你伤心 #
# 'Cause I never wanna see you sad #
# 我发誓愿与你分享一切喜悦与伤悲 #
# I swore to share your joy and your pain #
# 我将爱你不渝 #
# And I swear it all over again #
# 再来一遍 #
# A ll over again #
# 有人说 #
# Some people say #
# 世事终究有其尽头 #
# That everything has got its place in time #
# 白天会变黑夜 #
# Even the day must give way to the night #
# 但我不相信 #
# But I'm not buying #
# 因为在你的双眸之中 #
# 'Cause in your eyes #
# 我看见爱的火焰永恒的燃烧 #
# I see a love that burns eternally #
# 你在我眼中是如此的美丽 #
# And if you see how beautiful this looks to me #
# 你将知道我不会说谎 #
# You'll know I'm not lying #
# 当我们也曾经历分手的时刻 #
# Sure there'll be times we wanna say goodbye #
# 我们如果再努力一些 #
# But even if we try #
# 生命中有一些美丽,是无法轻言放弃的 #
# There are some things in this life won't be denied #
# 无法轻言放弃的 #
# Won't be denied #
# 我永远不会放手让你走 #
# I'm never gonna say goodbye #
# 我永远不愿见到你伤心 #
# 'Cause I never wanna see you cry #
# 我向你发誓,我的爱将直到永远 #
# I swore to you my love would remain #
# 我将爱你不渝 #
# And I swear it all over again and I #
# 我将永远不会伤害你 #
# I'm never gonna treat you bad #
# 我永远不愿见到你伤心 #
# 'Cause I never wanna see you sad #
# 我发誓愿与你分享一切喜悦与伤悲 #
# I swore to share your joy and your pain #
# 我将爱你不渝 #
# And I swear it all over again #
# 这一切越来越清晰 #
# The more I know of you, baby #
# 就发觉自己更加爱你 #
# I5 the more I know I love you #
# 我一直明了 #
# And the more that I'm sure #
# 我永远不会放手让你走 #
# I want you forever and ever more #
# 你越爱我 #
# And the more that you love me #
# 我越明白 #
# The more that I know #
# 我永远不会放手让你走 #
# Oh, that I'm never gonna let you go #
# 我要你明白 #
# Gotta let you know that I #
一起来
You sing.
# 我永远不会说再见 #
# I'm never gonna say goodbye # # I'm never gonna say goodbye #
# 我永远不愿见到你伤心 #
# 'Cause I never wanna see you cry # # Never wanna see you cry #
# 我向你发誓,我的爱将直到永远 #
# I swore to you my love would remain #
# 我将爱你不渝 #
# And I swear it all over again and I # # Swear it all over again and I #
# 我将永远不会伤害你 #
# I'm never gonna treat you bad # # Never gonna treat you bad #
# 'Cause I never wanna see you sad # # Never wanna see you sad #
# 我发誓愿与你分享一切喜悦与伤悲 #
# I swore to share your joy and your pain #
# 我将爱你不渝 #
# And I swear it all over again #
# 我永远不会说再见 #
# I won't say goodbye #
# 我永远不愿见到你伤心 #
# I won't see you cry #
# 我将永远不会伤害你 #
# I won't treat you bad #
# 我将永远看你伤心 #
# I won't see you sad #
# 我发誓 #
# This I swear #
好了 Croke Park
All right, Croke Park.
我要你们每个人举起手 像这样
We want everybody to put your hands up in the air like this.
然后从一边向另一边挥舞
And wa ve from side to side.
继续唱 这首歌叫Home
Sing along. This is called Home.
# 另一个夏季的一天来过又走 #
# Another summer day has come and gone away
# 在巴黎或罗马,但是我想回家 #
# In Dublin and Rome, but I wanna go home
# 虽然可能被百万人包围 #
# Maybe surrounded by a million people I #
# 但是仍然孤单 我想回家 #
# Still feel all alone, I just wanna go home #
# 我想你 #
# Oh, I miss you, you know #
# 我一直保留着我写给你的信 #
# But I've been keeping all the letters that I wrote to you #
# 每行"我很好 宝贝 你怎么样?" #
# Each one a line or two,"I'm fine, baby, how are you?"#
# 我寄出信 但是我知道这并不够 #
# Well, I would send them but I know that it's just not enough #
# 我的文字冰冷无味 #
# 'Cause my words were cold and flat #
# 但是你应该得到更多 #
# But you deserve more than that #
FEEHILY:跟我一起唱F,爱尔兰
EEHILY: Sing this with me, Ireland. #
# 另一架飞机 另一个夏天 #
# Another airplane, another sunny place #
# 很幸运我知道 我想回家 #
# I'm lucky I know but I wanna go home #
# 我要回家 #
# I've got to go home #
# 让我回家 #
# Let me go home #
# 离开你太远了 #
# I'm just too far from where you are #
# 我想回家 #
# I wanna go home, yeah #
# 让我回家 #
# Let me go home #
# 我开始了旅行 宝贝 #
# I've had my run Baby, I'm done #
# 我要回家 #
# I wanna go home #
# 我感觉我在和其他人生活 #
# And I feel just like I'm living someone else # 3 life #
# 就像一切都好时 我离开了 #
# It's like I just stepped outside when everything was going right #
# 我知道你为什么不愿意跟随我 #
# And I know just why you could not come along with me #
# 因为这不是你的梦 #
# 'Cause this was not your dream #
# 你总是信任我 #
# But you always believed in me #
# 又一个冬天来了又走 #
# Another winter day has come and gone away #
# 在巴黎或者罗马 我想回家 #
# In neither Paris nor Rome, but I wanna go home #
# 回家 回家 回家 #
# Go home, go home, go home, go home #
# 让我听到你的声音 #
Let me hear you, Dublin
# 让我回家 #
# Let me go home #
# I've had my run Baby, I'm done #
# 我在回家路上 #
# I'm coming back home #
# 让我回家 #
# Let me go home #
# 一切都会好起来 #
# It'll all be all right #
# 我将回家 #
# I'll be home tonight #
# 我正在回家 #
# I'm coming back home #
好了 Croke Park
Well, Croke Park...
你们感觉如何?
How are you all feeling now?
嗯 各位 该说再见的时候了
Well, guys, sadly the time has come for us to say goodbye.
我们也很害怕这一刻的到来 相信我
This is the moment that we've all been dreading, trust me.
今晚 是西城男孩的最后一夜
As tonight is, obviously, the very last night of Westlife,
真的要再见了 Croke Park
we certainly are going out in style, Croke Park, that's for sure-
当这支乐队在爱尔兰的西海岸创立的时候
You knom when this band started off back in the west coast of Ireland
我 Shane Mark在学校相遇
myselfi Shane and Mark met in school.
过了些日子 我们组建了乐队
And as time went on, we formed a little band.
那时的梦想很小
And that dream was very small.
就是录录唱片
The idea of just recording your own song,
也许有朝一日能够开我们的演唱会
maybe one day play your own concert.
时光流逝,我们的梦想变的越来越大
But as time went on, that dream got bigger and bigger.
我们碰到了一个叫Louis Walsh的家伙
We met a man called Louis Walsh
我们碰到Louis的时候 我们的一生改变了
When we met Louis, our lives certainly did change
之后我们遇到了Simon Cowell
We then met a man called Simon Cowell.
让我来告诉你们 Louis和Simon
And let me tell you, between Louis and Simon,
是我们今晚能站在这的主要原因
it's one the main reasons wh y we're stood here tonight.
对
Yeah.
之后呢 乐队变的越来越出名
And then it just got bigger and bigger.
我们开始了世界巡演
We started touring the world
每到之处 都有大批的粉丝人为我们尖叫
and everywhere we went, there was thousands of people screaming at us.
我们真的没想到
We didn't know what was happening.
现在 14年之后 我们该对所有人说再见了
And here we are, 14 years later, saying goodbye to it all.
和你们说 做这个决定真的很艰难
It's not an easy thing to do, let me tell you that.
我想说 Croke Park 非常感谢你
I just want to say, Croke Park, thank you so much-
你们一直很棒
You have been truly amazing.
我还有些话想对我妈妈说 今天她也在现场
I want to say a very special shout out to my mum who's here tonight.
几年前 我们失去了爸爸
A few years ago we lost our dad.
我知道 你在那 爸爸 我爱你
And I know you're up there, Dad. I love you very much.
感谢你给了生命
Thank you so much for giving me life.
我还想对我的兄弟姐妹们说
I wanna say a big shout out to all my brothers and sisters.
我非常爱你们
I love you guys so much.
还有 我生命中最重要的人
I wanna say a massive shout out to the most important person in my life,
我的妻子！ Jodi
my wife jodi
六个月前
Six months ago,
她给了我任何人都无法给予的礼物
she gave me the biggest present that anybody can ever give anyone.
我们的宝贝Koa
And that was our little boy Koa.
我告诉你 Croke Park 老话说得好
And I tell you what, Croke Park, it's very true what  you say,
"一段旅程结束后 新的旅程就要开始"
"As one journey ends, another one begins."
对于我和妻子和我们的孩子来说 我们的旅程才刚刚开始
And for me and jodi and our little bo y, our journe y's only beginning.
我爱你 宝贝
I love you very much, babe.
我想对站在那边的三个人说
I want to say to the three guys standing out here...
感谢你们 这一切真的太棒了
Thank you, guys, it's been truly amazing.
我永远爱你们
I'll love you forever.
还有Brain 他没在现场
And to Brian... Brian, who is not here tonight,
非常感谢你 Brain
thank you very much, Brian, for all the love
你总是向我们伸出援手
and all the time that you gave us when you were in the hand.
我们爱你 Brain 祝你幸福
We love you very much, Brian. We hope you're well.
好了 Croke Park 我该走了
That's it, Croke Park, I'm gonna go now
因为我要开始新的生活
'cause I'm gonna turn into a first class mess.
我真的很爱你们
I love you guys so much.
我们永远不会忘记今晚
We will never forget this night.
回去路上小心,Croke Park,再见
Have a safe journey home, Croke Park. Goodbye!
接下来
So...
Kian哭了
Kian cried.
Shane哭了
Shane cried.
搞不好我也会哭
That doesn't say much now if I don't cry.
站在这 一一说"感谢"
Standing up here trying to say"thank you"
对这14年受到的帮助 并不太容易
after 14 years is impossible.
我感谢 你们今晚在场的各位 不管是站着还是坐着
But I wanna say it to all of you standing here tonight, sitting here tonight,
还有在电影院看演唱会的观众以及工作人员
and to all the people around the place watching in cinemas and stuff,
14年后 我们还能在这的原因很简单
the reason we're here 14 years later is simple.
因为你们中的每一个人
It's down to each and every one of you guys
你们做的每一件事 观看的每一次巡演
for anything and everything you've done, for all the tours you've attendeaj
每一次你们站在酒店外等候我们 为我们尖叫
all the hotels you've stood outside and screamed and kept us awake,
所有你们买过的唱片
all the records you've bought,
你们给我们的每一个点点滴滴 真的太棒了
every little pieces of what you've given us. It's been amazing.
你们让我们的梦想一次次的成真
And you've made our dreams come true over and over again.
你们给了我们很多很多值得珍藏的回忆
And you've given us a million, million memories to take away with us
我们永远不会忘记
And that alone we'll never forget.
所以 今夜 请允许我 打从心底里
So, please, from the heart from me tonight,
说声感谢
Thank you very much for absolutely everything. I appreciate it.
时光飞逝 乐队越做越好
When the band started to get bigger and bigger as the days went by,
我们意识到我们所做的一切是多么的不可思议
We started to realize that what we were doing was something amazing, you know.
所有人也许愿意付出一切
Everybody and anybody would probably give anything
想要拥有同样的机遇
and love the opportunity to do what we've done.
去旅行 认识大咖
To travel and to, you know meet the people we've met,
和大咖同台
stood in the stages with the people we've stood on stages with.
我不得不说 过去那些日子太奇妙了
And I have to tell you, it's been absolutely incredible
我们爱这一切 我希望你们知道
We've loved it and I hope you know
当我们在其它国家演唱时
that when we were singing in every other country in the world
我们一直想做的是传播我们的文化
all we've ever wanted to do was  sewing the flag
成为你们的骄傲
and make you guys at home feel proud of us
爱尔兰的友好大使
and be ambassadors for Ireland.
我想对 Louis Walsh说感谢
I want to say a big thank you to Louis Walsh-
我永远不会忘记我到DART的那天
I'll never forget the day I got the DART,
我坐火车去试音
which is the train over here all I need to be audition.
我穿着黑上衣黑t恤 蓝裤子
And I was wearing a black suit with a black shirt and  blue trousers
唱了一首歌
And I got in and I sang a song.
然后出来一个人对我说
And the guy came up to me after and said,
Louis希望你加入他一个’酒吧乐队‘
"Louis Walsh wants you to be in his next 'pub' band."
我说:"我不想加入酒吧乐队
And I sad,"I don't want to be in a 'pub' band."
LOUIS 说的是流行乐队
With the way Louis talks, he said pop band
我搞错了
but I mistook it.
我非常高兴自己加入这个"酒吧乐队" 我们成功了 对吧?
So I'm glad I joined that"pub"band Louis, and we did all right?
我想对我的家人说谢谢
I wanna say a big thank you to my family.
我的妻子Georgina 15岁时 我遇见了她
To my beautiful wife Georgina who I met when I was 15.
G 我爱你
I love you with all my heart, G.
还有我的儿子Rocco and jay
And to my two little boys Rocco and jay,
你们是爸爸的心肝
the apple of their daddy's eye, I can tell you.
我做的一切都是为了他们
Everything I do is for them three, so...
我希望你们知道 我知道你们能懂我 感谢所有的一切
I hope you know that. I know you do, so thank you for everything.
还有我的哥哥和妹妹
To my brother and sister.
我的哥哥Adam 感谢你的一切付出
To my brother A dam, thank you for e veryt/ling, man
你是我坚强的后盾
You've been a rock of support and...
我知道你有6.45英尺,我才5.95英尺
I know you're six- foot- four- and- a- half and I'm five- foot- nine- and- a- half,
有些事是命中注定
but sometimes some things are meant to be.
所以我没法成为一名守门员 这也没关系啦
I tried and wouldn't be a goalkeeper and that might've been ok too.
Shay 今天也来了
Shay Given too here tonight,
我应该给他些钱作动力
and maybe I would've been giving Shay a run for his money.
我的妹妹 Gillian:"
To my sister Gillian,
我们一起长大 赛跑争夺
all of those years of growing up and racing down the stairs
一张看"星期六超级明星"的椅子
"to get the chair to watch Saturday Superstar.
你了解我
You know me and you...
Gillian本该是个超级明星
It shouldve been Gillian that was famous, really.
她才是家里真正的歌手
She was the real singer in the house.
当然 这里面不包括我爸爸
Of course, not including my dad.
Gillian已经有了一个幸福的家庭 还有3个宝宝Lexi Zack Mark
But, Gill, you've got a beautiful family, Lexi and Zack and Mark.
希望我们以后还能那么开心
And we've got a lot of great nights still ahead of us, hopefully.
感谢你们这些年的陪伴与付出
So, thank you for everything over the years.
还有我的妈妈
And to my mum.
我爱你 妈妈
I love you, Mum. lcan't... I can't even...
不管怎样 我都爱你
Anyway, Mum, I love you. You know I love you
你是我一直以来动力所在
and you've been an absolute tower of strength,
万分感恩
so thank you very much for absolutely everything.
我的三个兄弟Mark Shane and Kian
To my three boys Mark, Shane and Kian,
爱你们 感谢你们带给我的一切 每一件事
love you lads, thanks for everything. Thanks for absolutely everything.
你们一直不可思议
You've been unbelievable.
在我心中 你们无人能及 谢谢
obody can ever be the same. Thank you.
所以在场的朋友
To all my mates who are here as well,
从 Baldoyle远道而来的 所有支持过我们的人
everybody from Baldoyle and anybody who ever supported me,
感谢你们
thank you very much.
向你们致敬 谢谢
To you guys, thank you.
最后我想对我的父亲说谢谢
And I'n7 gonna leave my very last thank you to my dad.
爱你
Love you, man.
你一直对我说"事业为重"
You always used to say to me,"Do the business."
我希望我已经做到你说的
And I hope I have.
谢谢你 Dublin 晚安
Thank you, Dublin, and good night.
再见
I'll see you soon, bye- bye.
我试着不要哭出来
I'm gonna try not to cry.
我想以感谢我生命中最重要的两个人为开始
I wanna start off by thanking the two most important people in my life.
我知道大家支持我14年了
I know you guys have known us for 14 years,
但这两个人支持我不止14年
but these two people have supported me for a lot longer than 14 years,
我的爸爸妈妈 真心感谢
my mother and my father. Thank you so much.
他们就在那
They're over there.
我能有这么棒的父母
I couldn't ask to have two nicer people for parents.
我真的很幸运 爸爸妈妈 爱你们
'mjust a very lucky guy. I love you very much, Mum and Dad.
我的兄弟Barry Colin也在这
My two brothers Barry and Colin are here as well.
我们关系很好 有很多开心的时光
We're very close. We have a lot of fun together.
那时我家里充满了欢声笑语
There are a lot of laughs going on at my house at the moment
因为我们在一起
'cause they're living with me at the moment.
兄弟们 感谢你们
So, thank you very much, guys.
他们也把我的狗照顾的很好
They look after my dogs as well.
感谢 感谢 感谢
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
让我缓缓
OK I'll compose myself.
我的奶奶和姥姥 很幸运她们今天也在现场
Both my nanas. Very, very lucky that they're here this evening.
我很幸福 她们两都照顾过我
And I'm very lucky, they both sort of helped my mum to bring me up.
她们就在正对面 爱你们
They're up there anal literally, I love you both so much.
我从你们那里学到很多
You don't understand everything that I've learned from you both
还有我的祖父外祖父 我叫他们gaga
and also, obviously, both my granddads or as I call them Gaga and Gaga.
我爱你们
I love them very much, too.
你们对我的付出我难以回报
And I can't thank you enough for everything that you've done for me.
我还有很多亲戚在这
I've got so many cousins and aunties and uncles that are here, too.
所以 我的家人们 感激你们的支持
So, to all my family, thank you so much for supporting me
支持了我14年甚至更多
for the last 14 years and for a lot longer than that as well.
我在这认识了很多朋友
0K. I've got a lot of friends here.
有一些老朋友 还有新朋友
I've got some very, very old time friends and some new friends.
没有我的朋友...
And without my friends,
我就不能站在这个舞台上
I literally don't think I could be here on this stage.
你可能不理解这些对我来说多重要
You don't understand how much they mean to me.
我只能说感谢
Thank you, thank you.
以后你们可以用这件事跟我开玩笑
You can take the piss at me later for this.
谁是从Sligo来的?
Is there anyone here from Sligo?
因为我不得不说 我的家乡Sligo是一个充满魔力的小镇
'Cause I have to say, Sligo is a magical town to grow up in.
是一个音乐小镇
And it's such a musical town
它鼓励年轻人参与表演
It promotes young people to, sort of get into performance-
那是充满艺术的地方
You know it'sjust a very artistic place.
我想感谢Sligo 有这么好的成长环境
And I just wanna thank Sligo for being such a great place to grow up in,
真的
honestly, genuinely.
如果你还没去过那里 可以去看看
If you haven't been there, go and visit Sligo
相信我 你不会忘了那儿
'cause trust me, you won't forget it.
我和路易斯在离开westlife之后关系更亲密了
Myself and Louis, we're actually closer friends away from Westlife
与从前相比
than we are in Westlife.
我想他是世界上最幽默的人
He's the funniest man I actually think I know in the entire world.
所以路易斯 非常感谢你的支持 爱你
So, Louis, thank you so much for your support. Love you, too.
我还想对Caroline Downey说谢谢
I'd also like to say a big, massive thank you to Caroline Downey
他领我加入了ISPCC（爱尔兰防止虐待儿童协会）
who allows me to get really heavily involved in ISPCC,
我在那很快乐
which is a big joy for me and I love being involved in that.
Caroline非常感谢
So, thank you very much, Caroline,
感谢她为westlife做的一切
and everything that she's done for Westlife as well.
Childline 等等一切的一切 感谢你
Childline, etcetera, etcetera. Thank you, Caroline.
还有我所有的伙伴 我们庞大的团队
To all our massive crew. We bring a huge crew
你可以想象 这一路走来陪伴着我们
as you can imagine, on the road with us.
还有很多从Dublin来的朋友
There's also a lot of people from Dublin as well.
不仅仅是Dublin 还有当地的工作人员
And not just from Dublin. Our local crew as we call them
感谢你们
Thank you, guys. Thank you, thank you, thank you.
请为他们欢呼
Can we hear a big cheer for our crew please?
谢谢
Thank you.
三个伙伴在那
These three lads down here...
我不能告诉你们我们之间的故事 一点都不可以
Honestly, I couldn't even tell you that much of the stories that we have.
我会永远保密的
And they'll stay locked in a safe forever.
我们曾有过最辉煌的时代
'Cause we've had the best time that you could imagine we could have ever had.
到世界各地 乘飞机 巴士 到各大电台
Travelling the world you know on airplanes and buses, TV stations,
见到封面明星 见到Fair City里的演员
meeting megastars to meeting people from Fair City.
然后
And...
我们那么多开心的过往
Basically, we've literally had so much fun...
眼泪出来了 我并不想这样的
That kinda came out. I didn't really mean it to, sorry.
总之 感谢你们三个
Anyways, these three lad.s, thank you so much.
我爱你们 一生如此
I love you so much. Honestly, it's been the time of my life.
还有什么呢?
What else?
当然 还有你们每一个人 粉丝们 谢谢你们
Oh, yeah, of course, each and every one of you, the fans, thank you.
实话讲 众所周知
To be honest, 0K. it's well- known
你们支持我们 我们的音乐 我们的演唱会
that you support us and our music and our gigs,
但我最想感谢的是你们支持我们每一个人
but what I wanna say is that you supported each of us individually
伴随我们的跌宕起伏
through our various ups and downs in life.
你们是我们的朋友而不仅仅是粉丝
So, we really do look at you guys as our friends, not just our fans.
我们爱你们 你们每一个人
And we love each and every one of you to bits.
我是认真的
And I mean that.
现在 到该走的时候了
So, now I'm gonna go.
很高兴我没哭得很厉害
I didn't quite cry, so I'm happy with that.
Croke park,我爱你,我要离开你了
Croke Park, I'm gonna love you and leave you.
感谢这个夜晚 这真的是个超级棒的演唱会
Thank you so much for this evening. It's been a fantastic, fantastic show.
晚安,Shane先生该你了
Good night. Here's Mr. Shane for you.
人们经常问我们
People always ask us,
和西域男孩有关的回忆 最美好的哪一段?
you know"What's your favourite memory of Westlife?"
今晚就是我最美好的回忆 当下
Well, tonight is my favourite memory of Westlife. Right now.
瞧瞧
Looking out at this.
再没比这更大的场地了
It doesn't get any bigger than this, guys.
我们14年前从Sligo起航
You know we started off in Sligo 14 years ago.
当时只有二三十人来看我们的表演
Twenty, thirty people came to our gigs.
今天 我们有85000个观众
ow we've got 85,000.
搞忘感谢我背后的三个兄弟之前
Before I forget I want to thank the three boys behind me
我怕我会忘了
'cause I probably will forget I'm terrible like that.
过去14年来最好的三个朋友
My three best friends for the last 14 years.
我们一起环游世界 打破各类唱片记录
We travelled the whole world we broke all the records,
我们实现了一个乐队拥有的所有梦想
we've done everything a band could've wished for.
也是我们年少时所梦想的一切
That's all we wanted to be when we were younger.
我们想成为后街男孩那样的明星
We wanted to be pop stars like the Backstreet Boys or whoever it was.
14年了 我们实现了
And we got to do it. We got to do it for 14 years, guys,
一切都要归功于你们
and that's all thanks to every single person in here tonight...
是你们创造了这一切
...for making that happen.
还有Caroline Downey 让我们为她欢呼欢呼
A big shout out to Caroline Downey as well.
她参演了我们所有演唱会 自我们成立之初
She's put on all our gigs since we've started.
我知道今晚对Caroline来说 很特别
I know tonight's a special night for Caroline
这是一个壮观的夜晚
It is such a massive night.
从当初的第一个Childline演唱会
Our first gig was Childline, a long time ago.
到如今Croke Park连续两场演唱会
now we're playing to Croke Park for two nights,
真的难以置信
which is pretty incredible.
感谢我来自Sligo的朋友 还有其他地方的朋友
I want to thank my friends that are here from Sligo and from everywhere else.
你们知道的
Guys, you know who you are.
你们的友谊是我的一切
Your friendship has meant the world to me.
你们是我前进的动力
You know you've kept me on the straight and narrow for the whole time.
感谢你们
Thank you so much, guys.
我们一会儿喝一个
We'll have a pint of Guinness later on to celebrate.
你们可以欢呼了
I knew that'd get a cheer.
然后是我的兄弟姐妹
ext up is my brothers and sisters,
谢谢你们的关心 支持
Thanks for looking after me, guys, and being there for me.
我是老幺 当小不点的感觉还不赖
I'm the youngest of se ven kids, so it was nice to be the baby.
我有点被父母宠坏了
I got spoilt a little bit,
我也被我的兄弟姐妹宠坏了
but I got spoilt by my brothers and sisters as well.
谢谢你们 我爱你们
So, thank you, guys. I love you very much.
还有我们的经纪人Louis Walsh
I wanna say a big shout out to our manager Louis Walsh.
记得多年前我曾对路易斯说
I remember saying to Louis years ago,
当时我们在 the Point Depot做boyzone的暖场嘉宾
I think we were supporting Boyzone at the time in the Point Depot.
我对他:"你觉得我们能在这开演唱会吗?"
And I said to him,"Do you ever think we'll ever play this place?"
他说:"那是 当然"
And he was like... "Yeah, definitely."
"当然"
"Definitely."
我对他说:"真的吗?" 他说:"是的"
And I was like,"Seriously?"He was like,"Yeah."
后来我们在那开了73场演唱会
And we got to play it 73 times.
过去四年我们在Croke Park开了四次演唱会
And we got to play Croke Park four times in the last four years, guys.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
我做得很好,我们做到了
I'm doing well, I'm doing well. Getting through it.
感谢老爸老妈
I like to say a massive than you to my mum and dad.
作你们的儿子我感到很骄傲 感谢一切
I'm so proud to be your son. Thank you so much for everything.
我爱你们 你们懂的
I love you so much, you know that.
今晚在这个场馆里最重要的人是
The most important person in this stadium tonight
我美丽的妻子 Gillian
is my beautiful wife Gillian.
Gillian 我对你一见钟情 爱你至今
Gillian, I've loved you since I saw you for the first time
当时我们只有12岁
and we were only 12 years old.
追你追了好久 但我还是追到了
And it took me a long time to get you eventually, but I got you.
你那么支持我 只是...
And you stuck by me so well, it is just...
我无法描述对你的爱 这一切太不可思议了
I can't describe bow much I love you. It's just, it's indescribable.
你陪伴我经历风雨 让我学会专注
You knom you've kept me through... you've kept me focussed
无论发生什么
o matter what happens in our life.
专注手头的工作
You've always kept me focussed on the job in hand.
来到这 为在座的各位唱歌
To get out here and sing for all these people
做我所有想做的事 每次都如此 让我前进
and do whatever I ever wanted to do, you kept me going, every time.
我爱你 宝贝
I love you so much, babe.
你还带给我三个美丽 健康的孩子
You've given me three beautiful, healthy children.
这就是我们的一切 我爱你
And that's all we need, babe. That's all we need. I love you.
希望大家帮我一个忙
I want everybody to do me a favour.
每一个人... 如果你有手机的话
Now I want everybody to... If you have a mobile phone,
请打开手机里的电筒应用
please turn it on or turn on your little flashlight app.
如果在场的每位都有手机的话 希望你们能高举手机
Everybody in this has a phone, so I want everyone to hold it up high
我要讲一个小故事
I'm gonna tell you a quick little story.
我记得我18岁时对妈妈说
I remember when I was eight years old I said to my mum...
当时我正在看迈克尔杰克逊的视频
I was watching a video of Michael jacKson
我看的就是现在这样的景象
and all I saw was this on the telly.
我对妈妈说
Andlsaid to my mum...
"我有一天也会这样" 我说
I said,"That's gonna be me someday."
妈妈 我的梦想实现了
Well, Mum, my dream's come true
感谢你们
Thank you so much.
我想把下首歌献给我的爸爸妈妈
I want to dedicate this next song to my mum and dad
所有人的爸爸妈妈
all our mums and dads.
Nicky and Kevin看地上 感谢老天 停雨了
icky and Kevin looking down, thanks for stopping the rain for us.
我希望所有人都大声唱出这首歌
I want everybody to sing this really loud, Ok?
这是西城男孩的最后记忆 一起加油
This is our last memory of Westlife, so make it a good one.
# 当我失落时 我的灵魂疲倦 #
# When I am down and, oh, my soul's so weary #
# 困难来临,我心沉重 #
# When troubles come and my heart burdened be #
# 我静静的坚持、等待 #
# Then I am still and wait here in the silence #
# 直到你到来 坐在我身边 #
# Until you come and sit a while with me #
# 你鼓舞了我 我能攀上山峰 #
# You raise me up so I can stand on mountains #
# 你鼓舞了我 我能面对汹涌的大海 #
# You raise me up to walk on stormy seas #
# 大家一起唱起来 #
Sing it, everybody.
# 靠在你的肩膀上 我很坚强 #
CROWD: # I am strong when I am on your shoulders #
# 你鼓舞了我 让我超越自己 #
# You raise me up to more than I can be #
# 环顾四周 #
Take a look around.
# 你鼓舞了我 我能攀上山峰 #
# You raise me up so I can stand on mountains #
# 你鼓舞了我 我能面对汹涌的大海 #
# You raise me up to walk on stormy seas #
# 靠在你的肩膀上 我很坚强 #
# I am strong when I am on your shoulders #
# 你鼓舞了我 让我超越自己 #
# You raise me up to more than I can be #
# 你鼓舞了我 我能攀上山峰 #
# You raise me up so I can stand on mountains #
# 你鼓舞了我 我能面对汹涌的大海 #
# You raise me up to walk on stormy seas #
# 靠在你的肩膀上 我很坚强 #
# I am strong when I am on your shoulders #
# 你鼓舞了我 让我超越自己 #
# You raise me up to more than I can be #
# 你鼓舞了我 我能攀上山峰 #
# You raise me up so I can stand on mountains #
# 你鼓舞了我 我能面对汹涌的大海 #
# You raise me up to walk on stormy seas #
# 靠在你的肩膀上 我很坚强 #
# I am strong when I am on your shoulders #
# 你鼓舞了我 让我超越自己 #
# You raise me up to more than I can be #
# 你鼓舞了我 #
# You raise me up #
# 让我超越自己 #
# To more than I can be #
谢谢
Thank you.
我要大声对Lily和在这的所有人说
I'm gonna say a big shout out to my nana Lily as well who's here tonight.
谢谢
Thank you.
# 歌名 We got a little world of our own #
# We got a little world of our own #
# 你让我开心 #
# You make me feel funny #
# 当你来到我身边 这就是我的发现,honey #
# When you come around Yeah, that's what I found out, honey #
# 没有你我会怎样 #
# What am I doing without you? #
# 你让我幸福 #
# You make me feel happy #
# 当我离开你时 总能想起你 #
# When I leave you behind, it plays on my mind nom honey #
# 没有你我该怎么办 #
# What am I doing without you? #
# 珍藏我们所有的过去 #
# Oh, took for granted everything we had #
# 如果我找到一个人,像极了你 #
# As if I'd find someone who'sjust like you #
你们大家一起来！
Sing, Ireland! Come on!
# 我们住在镇上的一处 #
# We got a little world of our own #
# 我给你讲我自己的秘密 #
# I'll tell you things that no one else knows #
# 让你走进我内心深处 #
# I let you in where no one else goes #
# 没有你我该怎么办 #
# What am I doing without you? #
# 我一直在找寻的 #
# And all of the things I've been looking for #
# 就在我的门外 #
# Have always been here outside of my door #
# 我一直在发现新意 #
# And all of the time I'm looking for something new #
# 大家一起唱 #
You sing! #
# 没有你我该怎么办 #
# What am I doing without you? #
# 我想我已经准备好 #
# Well, I guess I'm ready #
# 安定下来不在四处漂泊 #
# For settling down And fooling around is over #
# 结束了 宝贝 #
# It's over, baby #
# 我发誓 一切都是真的 #
# And I swear that it's true #
# 没有意外 没有意外 #
# No buts or maybes # No buts or maybes #
# 当我遭受挫折 总有人拯救我 #
# When I'm falling down, there's always someone who saves me #
# 拯救我的那个人 #
# Someone who saves me #
# 就是你 #
# And girl it's you #
# 有趣,生活为什么充满这么多惊喜 #
# Oh, funny how life can be so surprising #
# 我才开始了解你在做什么 #
# I'm just realising what you do #
# 我们住在镇上的一处 #
# Oh We got a little world of our own #
# 我给你讲我自己的秘密 #
# I'll tell you things that no one else knows #
# 让你走进我内心深处 #
# I let you in where no one else goes #
# 没有你我该怎么办 #
# What am I doing without you? #
# 我一直在找寻的 #
# And all of the things I've been looking for #
# 就在我的门外 #
# Have always been here outside of my door #
# 我一直在发现新意 #
# And all of the time I'm looking for something new #
# 没有你我该怎么办 #
# What am I doing without you? #
# 感觉很棒,你也去感受 #
# Well, it's feeling right now # Feel it right now #
# 让我们从现在开始,让我从们现在开始 #
# So let's do it right now # Let's do it right now #
# 祈祷你能理解 #
# Praying that somehow you will understand the way #
# 现在感觉很棒,你也去感受 #
# It's feeling right now # Feeling right now #
# baby,我不会让这些流逝 #
Baby, somehow I won't let this slip away #
Croke Park,挥舞你们的双手
Croke Park, clap your hands!
# 我们住在镇上的一处 #
# Oh, we got a little world of our own #
# 我给你讲我自己的秘密 #
# I'll tell you things that no one else knows #
# 让你走进我内心深处 #
# I let you in where no one else goes #
# 没有你我该怎么办 #
# What am I doing without you? #
# 我们住在镇上的一处 #
# We got a little world of our own #
# 我给你讲我自己的秘密 #
# I'll tell you things that no one else knows #
# 让你走进我内心深处 #
# I let you in where no one else goes #
大家一起来
You sing it!
# 没有你我该怎么办 #
# What am I doing without you? #
# 我一直在找寻的 #
# All of the things I've been looking for #
大声唱！
Louder!
# 就在我的门外 #
# Have always been here outside of my door #
一起来
Come on!
# 我一直在发现新意 #
# And all of the time I'm looking for something new #
# 我们住在镇上的一处,我们住在 #
# We got a little world of our own # We got a little #
# 我给你讲我自己的秘密 #
# I'll tell you things that no one else knows #
# 镇上的一处 #
# World of our own #
# 让你走进我内心深处 #
# I let you in where no one else goes # I let you in where no one goes #
# 我一直在找寻的 #
# And all of the things I've been looking for #
# 所有东西 #
# And all of the things #
# 就在我的门外 #
# Have always been here outside of my door #
# 我一直在找寻的 #
# I've been looking for #
# 我一直在发现新意 #
# And all of the time I'm looking for something new #
# 镇上的一处 #
# World of our own #
# 我们住在镇上的一处,我们住在镇上的一处 #
# We got a little world of our own # We got a little world of our own #
# 我给你讲我自己的秘密 #
# I'll tell you things that no one else knows #
# 让你走进我内心深处 #
# I let you in where no one else goes #
# 镇上的一处 #
# World of our own #
# 我一直在找寻的 #
# And all of the things I've been looking for #
# 就在我的门外 #
# Have always been here outside of my door #
# 我一直在发现新意 #
# And all of the time I'm looking for something new #
# 我们住在 #
# Say, we've got a little #
# 镇上的一处 #
# World of our own #
# 让你走进我内心深处 #
# I let you in where no one else goes #
# 我一直在找寻的 #
# And all of the things I've been looking for #
# 没有你我该怎么办 #
# What am I doing without you? #
# 我们住在镇上的一处 #
# We got a little world of our own #
(欢呼)
Whoo!
# 每个人都在找寻新的事物 #
# Everybody's looking for that something #
# 万事俱备,只欠它 #
# One thing that makes it all complete #
# 你在陌生地点找到 #
# You'll find it in the strangest places #
# 地点让你意想不到 #
# Places you never knew it could be #
# 有的在小朋友的脸上 #
# Some find it in the face of their children #
# 有的在爱人的眼里 #
# Some find it in their lover's eyes #
# 没人能否定它带来的欢乐 #
# Who can deny the joy it brings #
# 当你找到它 #
# When you've found that special thing? #
一起唱
You sing.
# 你不用翅膀便能飞 #
# You're flying without wings #
# 有的在每天清晨 #
# Some find it sharing every morning #
# 有的在他们的独居生活里 #
# Some in their solitary lives #
# 你在别人的世界里找寻 #
# You'll find it in the words of others #
# 简单的界限便能让你欢喜让你哭泣 #
# A simple line can make you laugh or cry #
# 你在深厚的友谊中找寻 #
# You'll find it in the deepest friendship #
# 你珍视生命 #
# The kind you cherish all your life #
# 你理解这件事的意义 #
# And when you know how much that means #
# 你找到那个特别的东西 #
# You've found that special thing #
# 你不用翅膀便能飞 #
# You're flying without wings #
# 多么不可思议 #
# So impossible as it may seem #
# 你可以为所有梦想战斗 #
# You've got to fight for every dream #
# 因为没人知道哪个能让你有成就 #
# 'Cause who's to know which one you let go #
# 会让你完整 #
# Would have made you complete #
# 对我来说 就是在你身旁醒来 #
# Well, for me, it's waking up beside you #
# 看到阳光打在你的脸上 #
# To watch the sunrise on your face #
# 知道我可以对你说我爱你 #
# To know that I can say,"I love you"#
# 在有限的时空中 #
# In any given time or place #
# 我知道的 #
# The little things that only I know #
# 就是把你拥有 #
# Those are the things that make you mine #
# 没有翅膀却能飞 #
# And it's like flying without wings #
# 因为你就是我的唯一 #
# 'Cause you're my special thing #
# 我没有翅膀却能飞 #
# I'm flying without wings #
# 你就是我生命的意义 #
# And you're the place my life begins #
# 我陪你到老 #
# And you'll be where it ends #
# 我没有翅膀却能飞 #
# I'm flying without wings #
# 你带来快乐 #
# And that's the joy you bring #
# 宝贝 我没有翅膀却能翱翔 #
# Oh, baby, I'm flying without wings #
爱你
Love you!
Love you.
谢谢 爱尔兰
Thank you very much, Ireland.
再见
Goodbye.